And my potential is seeing everyone’s feelings
Who else here has it out for me?
It’s you who leaked the photo
Let’s just say I have a video clip that you don’t want others to see
What video clip?
I’m taking it off.
When you can’t control other people
why don’t you accept who you are?
Can you accept if I told you I see you as a good friend?
I’m okay.
The reason I don’t want to tell my crush about myself?
It’s because I never know what he’s feeling
About that clip, I would understand if
Forget about it
But you’ve always wanted to know about me
I do. I think it could be good for our relationship
Wait, our relationship?
Hello.
My name is Punn Taweesilp
I am in M.4, Head Student of the Gifted Program
Many think I am perfect, but I don’t agree.
I have to say, I’ve never met a student as perfect as you
The problem is we can’t decide how to utilize this perfection
in the upcoming Academic Excellence Competition
What do you say, Mr. Pom?
Mr. Pom probably wants to hog his Gifted student
and doesn’t want him to help us.
That’s not true.
I’m willing to have my Gifted students enter this competition.
But I don’t understand why you all want only Punn
Wasuthorn can enter the math event.
But Wave won’t do it.
It can be any student from other classrooms
There are other talented students here.
Compete in the Language event
Math.
Sports.
But you like music
Settle down.
Why do we make him choose based on his competency?
Some kid is competent in all the subjects.
Isn’t that right, Punn?
Can I compete in all events?
Your father will be so proud, I believe so.
I am highly competent in music and arts
Can we practice in the actual venue?
We are the Gifted. Of course, we can.
Perfect.
The flow wasn’t right at first
The rhythm was a little off towards the end.
We will get there with some practice
You forgot one move
What move?
The finale. You didn’t kiss me
Practice is practice. You can’t just play around
Will a little romance kill you?
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Punn!
Let’s continue with the practice.
I know you’re just pretending to be mad
I don’t want it anymore
Come on
Punn, let go of me.
I won’t… not until…
Fine, I’m not mad anymore.
No
Not until I want to let go.
You have a way with words, don’t you?
Do you like it?
Yes.
Punn!
Where did you go?
It’s almost 7 PM. Let’s call it a day
I have to practice my speech
Punn,
I know you’re a super-perfectionist.
But I want to you enjoy it while you dance.
Why, don’t I look happy?
Your color clearly tells me you’re under pressure.
If only there were 72 hours in a day
How about this? Send me your life schedule
I’ll manage it for you.
I’ve got to go.
Hey, wait. Please sign here.
Punn, are you left-handed?
Yes.
Let’s talk about a recent tragedy.
An Olympiad gold medalist committed suicide
This is a trending topic in an online community right now
A question has been asked.
Is a talented student often miserable?
Today, we have a chat with a man who can best answer the question,
Prof. Dr. Premchai Taweesilp,
Deputy Permanent Secretary of the Ministry of Education.
First, I’d like to express my condolences to the deceased’s family.
On the topic of a talented student being miserable,
I’ve been hearing this for years.
And I ask myself, when can we get rid of this 50- year-old myth
about us being a developing country?
Japan transformed from a country that lost a war
to a world leader in innovation
How did they do that?
Certainly not because they think talented people are miserable.
Today, we need to stimulate our kids to develop to their full potential
So, they can help develop our country
If we continue with this kind of false thinking,
we will be left behind.
How long can you pretend that your life is so great?