Good job, Namtaan.
You’ve made significant progress in developing your potential
This is a tear
Mr. Chanon Taweepong.
He was in classroom one when he enrolled in the Gifted Program
He’s a Gifted student in my year.
Do you remember his signature?
It was signed by Mr. Pom’s pen
Are you saying Mr. Pom is hiding something from us?
P’ Chanon didn’t resign
He found out the secret of the school.
Namtaan!
After I went in the warehouse, I passed out immediately
I didn’t see anything.
The Director has selected the Head Student
It was Punn
If you’ve read fictions about kids with superpowers,
you’d know that the storylines are not much different.
It starts with a kid living in a boring world
She herself is boring. Her words are boring.
Everything is so boring
Aren’t you bored listening to the story of a dorky girl
who overused her power and got a seizure?
What’s that? What happened?
Oh my gosh. Boring!
All of you should join different clubs to develop your potential
based on your interest.
I want to join the Nursing Club
Why don’t you join a Detective Club?
Isn’t poking your nose in other’s business your kind of fun?
Can I join the Joke Club?
How about the morgue?
That’s where all your jokes end up.
Is it okay to not have any club?
Is it okay to not have charisma?
There’s a long list of things you don’t have.
Anyone else would like to join a club?
Ahem, I do.
You’ve seen enough of boring villains
Allow me to take you on a sassy journey
of the sassiest Gifted student.
I will join the Drama Club
Cue the music
Hi everyone, my name is Best.
I’m the Director
I want everyone to introduce themselves
and give a line that you prepared
We’ll go by a numerical order
Let’s start with the prince.
Okay, go.
Hi, my name is Fluke from classroom 4/7.
All heroines have dreams.
For me, it’s acting
even though I have to use my potential to the best of my ability
And my potential is
seeing everyone’s feelings.
My dearest Princess Vivienne.
People’s feelings manifest themselves to me in colors.
Yellow means confidence.
Orange means happiness.
Now, for the role of the princess
Purple means fear.
My superpower enables me to understand how others feel
If you’re this scared, you should just go home and cry like a baby.
And use it to destroy my competition effectively
No one will stand in my way.
The rising star now is Clair from the Gifted Program
This one.
Finally, I, Vivienne, was crowned Queen of the White City
I have entitled the honors and power
Wrong!
Honors and rights, not power.
Entitled the honors and rights
It’s just a coronation speech
Is it necessary to follow the script word by word?
Hey, Cha-em.
If you can’t act, at least do a good job of making the costumes.
Yes, mam.
Like any tale, where there is a princess,
there is a green-eyed monster lurking behind.
Green means jealousy.
Are you all right?
I’m fine
Pangrum, you are my friend, aren’t you?
I invited you to eat with me during lunch
I talked to the director to get you a supporting role in this play.
Tell me, besides Cha-em, who else here has it out for me?
No one. Don’t assume the worst
Really?
Yes.
No one my ass. This one is green. That one is green.
Sure, if this is how you’re going to play
I know that by being special due to being Gifted and getting the lead role
I can be an object of hatred.
The solution is…
The solution is so easy.
Love triangle.
With my potential, within just one week
I’ve gathered all the information of everyone’s feelings about one another.
The way people with the upper hand deal with those beneath them is
to make them hate one another
Best, you jerk!
The male lead has yet to come out of the closet.
When everyone turns on each other,
the throne of the White City is securely under my control
I haven’t heard you play this song before
I’ve just tried it today
What’s that?
My costume.
I’m getting it fixed
It looks like a shroud
I think it looks fine
It looks fine but is that enough for a female lead?
Never mind.
By the way, have you told your dad you’re the Head Student?
I’ve texted him, but we haven’t talked.
Don’t be upset. Your dad is not good at expressing his feelings
But trust me, he’s proud of you.
You’re perfect. There’s no reason he won’t be.
How come you know so much about my dad?
You’ve told me, and I remember it all
Your childhood, your family.
Everything you’ve told me is all here in my brain
When will you tell me about yours?
Do you really want to know?
If you want to tell me, I do want to know.
The reason I don’t want to tell my crush about myself?
It’s because I never know what he’s feeling.
He shows a range of colors.
I can never know after he hears my story,
what color it will be.
I told you the costume can’t be fixed in time.
The play will debut in a few days.
Do you expect Costume to work on yours only?
We have other things to do.
I’m the female lead. My costume should be the most important
Other people’s costumes are important, too.
I don’t know. If the costume isn’t beautiful, I won’t wear it.
And stop asking questions.
If I keep on talking, my facial mask will break
I’m hanging up.
It may sound over the top.
But for a heroine, a beautiful image is the most important
A girl like me cannot be tainted
In the Name of the Moon
And this is where the whole story begins.
The person who leaked my photo is in this club.
I will look at every single person’s feelings