Are you okay?
I’m totally fine. Never mind.
Mon enters the competition, too.
That’s because her potential is limited to sports.
But you black out
You’re this way because you’ve exercised too much of your potential
You’re weak.
Get out!
Weirdo!
Punn has resigned from his Head Student role
I have some ideas about what I’ll do as the new Head Student
"Our heroine wins gold medals in all sports events.
Ms. Patcharamon Pitiwongkorn, M.4/2 (Gifted)."
Next up is ‘Gossip ‘til We Drop’.
In the latest update, the Gifted Program had a switch
in the Head Student role
The main characters are the two students who got in a fight earlier.
This may intensify the rift within the class even further.
Boom! Vroom! Vroom! Vroom!
Next up, our school is as weird as the weather right now
The bras of female students are being stolen
Ms. Ladda can’t find the culprit yet.
What’s wrong with everyone?
This looks like a zombie movie
How did it end up like this?
Two days earlier
As you may know, Punn has resigned as the Head Student.
It is necessary for me to select the new Head Student.
We’ve made the selection based on the list submitted earlier
The new Head Student is ...
Wave
Wave, do you want to say something to your friends?
As the new Head Student,
there’s something I’ve always wanted to do.
I want to see us improved.
I want to see everyone develop to their full potential.
Is this really him?
First, we need to tie some loose ends
For example, we need to deal with those who ditch the class often.
All right, it is him.
Uh huh.
And those who have yet to discover their potential.
To give a nudge to them to study harder,
I want those who haven’t discovered their potential
to maintain the classroom
and clean the room every day
until they find their potential
Son of a bitch…
Why are you doing this?
To motivate them
If they don’t want to be on the cleaning duty
they should focus more on finding their potential
Who knows?
They may find out their potential is cleaning.
Or they may have already known that they don’t have any potential
This will be a wakeup call for them to realize that they don’t belong here
and resign from the Program.
If you think this will help your friends develop their potentials
we can give it a try.
What the hell?
Go back to your seat.
Let’s start the class.
Oh, the Director
I’m so sorry
You gave me such a warm welcome.
What brings you here?
I want to talk to Patchamon.
Mon isn’t in the Gifted class today.
That’s fine
What were you upset about?
I was quite stressed about my potential
Why?
I think that I may not have any
It’s been months and I haven’t found anything
that could be my potential.
I understand you, Pawaret
But each of us moves at our own pace.
Just because you haven’t found your potential today
doesn’t mean that you don’t have it
The difficulty in finding your potential
may make it greater than anyone else’s once you find it.
I’m not sure about that.
Relax.
You may have been focusing too hard on it.
Try to do what you don’t usually do.
Or talk to your friends
whom you don’t usually talk to.
You may understand more.
What do you mean?
Our school is as weird as the weather right now.
The bras of female students are being stolen
Ms. Ladda can’t find the culprit yet.
Be careful, girls.
Next up is ‘Gossip ‘til We Drop’.
Come and shower me with gossip
Let me go!
You startled me.
What do you want with me?
The Director asked me to give this document to you
And I want to see where you’ve been off to.
Why, do you want to join my club?
I want you to do three things
Duck, kick and run
Huh?
Duck!
Kick!
Run!
We lost again.
What are you guys playing?
Jane set up a bet whether you can knock out
everyone in the club within 10 minutes.
Less than 10
She hasn’t broken a sweat.
As promised, everyone,
Jane will tidy up the gym today.
Congratulations!
Wait, stop. This is silly
What if I accidently broke someone’s neck?
Calm down,
drink this to cool down
Come on, throw it.
I think we should go.
No reason to be the front tire of a tricycle.
What?
A third wheel
Who’s this?
My friend
So, what are you doing here?
Are you here to join the club?
Not really. I just want to have a look.
We will practice soon.
I’ll show you. Let’s go.
Pang, come here.
This is the practice place
In the National Youth Games,
Coach will send you instead of Jane.