Making things disappear is my true potential
Did you make Folk disappear?
I can’t even control my own power.
You must bring it back
You need to feel guilty and want Folk to come back
Folk, can you hear me?
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
You’re one of those Gifted kids
Who’s that Gifted kid?
Every potential has a cause and effect
Namtaan has a power to know stuff about other people
because she is a… curious person.
I touched an object and saw strange images.
It’s a flashback of what the item has been through in the past
Who’s Medfai?
How is it going, Namtaan?
This type of indie music… it must be Korn’s
Next item.
If you’ve read fictions about kids with superpowers,
you’d know that the storylines are not much different
It starts with a kid living in a boring world
until one day everything changes for the better
Being left under the bed for so long that it’s covered in dust…
This must be Ohm’s.
On to the last one.
Give it a try.
This one is yours.
It is a gift given to you on your 15th birthday
You’ve kept it close to you ever since.
I’ve used this pen for 12 years.
Good job, Namtaan.
You’ve made significant progress in developing your potential.
I used to think that it was just an imagination.
Why the numbers are rising so high?
Until the day I had a real superpower.
Are you hiding anything from me?
She’d got so much better over the past few years
Why has she gone back to when she was sick?
What is your Gifted program anyway?
As I have mentioned to you, Namtaan is gifted
She’d also had abnormally high blood pressure since she was young
If not controlled properly, she may have a seizure and become paralyzed
Mom!
If something worse happens, will it be worth it?
There’s nothing to be worried, I can guarantee
I opposed the idea since she was transferred here.
As a kid with a superpower,
I don’t know how high the expectations people have of me are.
But I have quite a high expectation of myself.
I want to be a doctor.
Not only to cure myself, but I also think that
if I can make it, my mom will be proud.
Can I have an answer that is not the version you give to adults?
I don’t know.
I used to read a novel
The heroine is a detective with a psychic power
It was fun but it’s just a novel.
For a special person, whatever she wants to do, she can do it.
Thank you.
Okay, each potential is caused by a different reason
No matter what it is, the best way to maintain it
is to gain more knowledge through reading.
I have prepared each of you a list of books to read,
based on your potential and passion
Claire, why don’t you tell me about your passion?
You may get a few books to read this week.
I don’t have any particular passion.
I just know that I must be famous.
Luckily, I was born in an era when social media can help me with that
I don’t have to waste time in the library.
Social media makes people narcissists
You can’t make yourself a lead star in a story
if you don’t read enough about it
He may just want to avoid you
Pang! Ohm!
What are you chatting about?
Your friend is speaking. Are you listening?
Let me tell you.
All Gifted students can be anything they want after they graduate
But those who don’t apply themselves may not graduate
Here are your books.
Why do I have to read so much?
Don’t complain. You have only 4 books.
Look at mine. I have 8.
Your ones look much more interesting.
If I read all of mine, I’d be like Einstein
Our potentials are different.
You focus on physics
But I need to read from myths and folklore
to the cosmos, astronomy and history…
Stop right there.
Let me go back to my Theory of Relativity
Look at Pang. He hasn’t discovered his potential yet
but he’s much more attentive than you.
Pang!
Buried deep in your book.
You’re so diligent.
I thought you’re better than this
What?
I was just playing one game
You’re looking at me like I’ve killed someone
You didn’t kill anyone but time
Mr. Pom asked us to use this time to discover your potential,
not to play a game.
I just don’t get why he needed us to read so many books
Not everyone enjoys reading like you do
I know but can’t you just do it for your own future?
How can you be sure that if you do what you’re told,
you will have a bright future?
What reason do you have not to do it?
You’ve made the effort just to prove your point?
To clear any doubts about the future of our seniors who graduated.
Hey, it features our photos, too.
This is the latest version.
Why is there only one student in the first class?
Mr. Pom said that the earliest classes would have only 1-2 students.
The number has increased to 10 over the last couple of years
Don’t get dragged into this.
The student from the first year won a gold medal
from the Chemistry Olympiad competition.
She’s come up with a technique to kill cancer cells
and been awarded by the UNESCO.
There are two students from the second year.
One went to study at MIT
and works as a research physical scientist.
The other is a diplomatic attaché in the UK.
The next one is Mr. Porama Wongratana, Year Three, ID: 004
Hey, this is Mr. Pom. He looked like a dork.
Mr. Pom got a Master’s Degree in Neuroscience from Boston.
He became a teacher to help the Director develop our potentials
Next up: Mr. Kamthorn Ratanakachorn, Year Three, ID: 006.
Ethnicity: Thailand, Nationality: Thailand, Religious: Buddhism.
Wait!
What are you doing?
Strange.
The Gifted ID runs sequentially from Year One, doesn’t it?
Why does it skip 005?
Must be a technical error.
That shouldn’t happen with the Gifted Program
What are you doing?
That yearbook is the newest version.
It must have been edited
If we want to know who 005 is,
we need to look at an older version.
Wait, Pang.
I should have believed you
I shouldn’t have let her drag me into this.
Year three falls in Academic Year 2006, right?
Yes.
We need to find the one published in that year
Pang!
You’re having too much fun here.
Here it is.
This one was published in 2006
the year Mr. Pom enrolled in this Program
No. 005 may not even exist
This is a tear
Is it possible that the missing page contains the info of 005?
Wait, how is this important?
Gifted Student No. 005: Mr. Chanon Taweepong.
Born on 24 June 1990.
He was in classroom one when he enrolled in the Gifted Program
Why has his info page been torn off?
You don’t believe he quit the program, do you?
Let’s do something fun.