IT’S RAINING (HEAVILY) ON THE LAST DAY OF FILMING.
OK. Cut!
The slate, please. I need two claps.
We’re doing a close-up shot, right?
Right.
I’m having goosebumps.
It was full of emotions.
It was somehow weird to see two of my friends kissing.
[NOT USED TO SEEING THAT.]
I was so into it
and having chills at the same time.
I like it though, the last scene.
The emotions were so on point.
[THE RAIN IS POURING AGAIN.]
Staff: It’s pouring.
Staff: What are you going to do, Mr. Director?
Well, we flew kites in the rain before.
But we can’t kiss in the rain here.
[TOO HEAVILY!]
We just can’t.
Staff: Hi, guys.
Staff: What time is it now?
I don’t know. I have nothing to say.
[SO MANY PROBLEMS!]
It’s 2:28 am right now.
And what’s happening is…
It’s been raining since 11 pm.
It’s been 3-4 hours now,
and there are 4 scenes altogether that have been adjusted to the new direction.
They were turned into indoor scenes.
The rain hasn’t stopped.
All we can do is pray.
Please stop. We need to continue filming with a nicer atmosphere.
Staff: And it’s a very important scene for today.
Right.
We only have 2 scenes left here.
[ONLY TWO AND WE’LL BE DONE!]
And everyone will get to go home and rest peacefully.
Then we can proudly say we’re done filming.
You can rain as much as you want but can I please get the kiss scene…
Finished?
Yes!
Or you can rain the second half because that last scene is more flexible.
But we can’t kiss in the rain, seriously.
Please. I’m begging you.
[THE RAIN HAS STOPPED.]
Nanon, you’re repeating the lines, right?
Yes, to wake myself up.
[NANON, YOU JUST TOOK A NAP, RIGHT?]
I’m so ready!
Cut.
[HE’S STILL CRYING SO HARD.]
Can I get some tissue papers, please?
I’m here to support my friends.
There are lots of obstacles filming this scene.
The rain, the sleepiness, everything.
But I do believe that Ohm and Nanon can pull it off.
Right.
All the obstacles are here to test us.
To make us do better.
Staff: The whole crew has been tested today.
Exactly!
But it’s specialness.
Don’t blackout yet.
It’s special…it’s late, right? You’re sleepy.
I am.
It is very special.
Shh! They’re starting now.
There was something that we don’t need, like the tears.
But I do understand the emotions you had there.
[P’AOF DOESN’T WANT THE TEARS.]
But the character Pat didn’t need that.
The tears.
That’s the problem.
I was giving him choices in just case.
[IN CASE P’AOF NEEDS IT LATER.]
No, I’m serious.
In case you want it.
Kiss scene at 4 am.
To be honest, having to wait to film affected my mood.
I could concentrate more.
Right, you got to rest for a bit.
That too.
No, I didn’t get to rest but…
it dragged me deep into concentration.
I felt like I really needed to finish the shooting.
But at the very beginning, I just wanted to party.
‘I’m going to find a better hero for the play.’
‘I’m done asking you.’
[THE LAST SCENE, EVERYONE.]
Cut.
Ohm and Nanon, come here at the monitors.
I’m here.
Ohm.
I’ll let you say ‘The filming is done.’
Here. The filming is done, buddy!
What?
The filming is done, buddy.
The filming is done, buddy!!
I thought he was going to brief us on something.
Exactly. I thought the same.
Great job.
Thank you.
Thank you, Nanon.
Thank you, Ohm.
[LET’S GO BACK BEFORE THE RAIN.]
This is the last day of filming.
[LET’S GO GET SOME PICTURES.]
I’m just playing around.
Staff: Who else is here tonight?
Everyone who works on this series,
including those who finished their scenes earlier. Let’s go take
some pictures of the last day, guys.
Hi.
He’s even wearing a suit.
Do you like men in suits?
You look better without it.
I’m just kidding.
I asked Prom once what he’d wear on the last day of filming.
I teased him that he’d be wearing Gucci or brand name stuff all over.
[NANON, HE’S SUCH A TEASE.]
Just like I said.
Louise Vuitton sandals.
Pants from Chanel.
T-shirt from Chanel.
And the suit?
Borrowed.
[THE JOKE ENDS HERE.]
Let’s say hey!
The filming is done, buddy!!
“So grateful to everyone who has always been supportive. Every piece of feedback, complaint, and compliment is much appreciated. I thank you from the bottom of my heart. Until we meet again, buddy. - P’Aof, The Director.”
WATCH RERUNS OF EVERY EPISODE ON WETV.