[OHM WANTS TO JOIN.]
[OHM’S NEW TOY.]
[IT’S A NEW SONG. LET HIM REHEARSE IT FIRST.]
♪ Is love a beautiful world? ♪
♪ Something of grandeur ♪
♪ Is it a sky, a mountain, a sea, or other kind of splendor? ♪
♪ Just a love song that you… ♪
[WHAT ARE THE LYRICS AGAIN?]
Sometimes, I forget. You know?
WE MUST WELCOME THE NEW SONG WITH A BEAUTIFUL SCENE.
♪ There are no perfect… ♪
♪ There are no perfect sweet… ♪
[HE FORGETS THE CHORDS TOO.]
And now I’m forgetting the chords.
[SORRY. IT’S THE FIRST REHEARSAL OF THE SONG.]
♪ There are no perfect sweet words ♪
♪ Love is nothing else but you ♪
Staff: You basically sing to the audience?
Yes, to end the episode beautifully.
Everyone will get to hear a very good song.
Staff: What is the song called?
It’s called Our Song (The Song I Just Finished Composing).
Staff: Really?
Staff: You just finished it?
Just now.
What a genius* (Genius = Achariya).
I’m not talking about myself.
[THANK YOU FOR SUCH A BEAUTIFUL SONG, P’AMP.]
I meant P’Amp Achariya, the composer.
♪ Or read between the lines ♪
♪ I can’t make sense of what you’ve done ♪
[YOU’RE VERY JUMPY!]
♪ I’ve now realized what my love is about ♪
♪ It’s something small that I just can’t live without ♪
[THAT’S A VERY NICE SONG.]
Okay. Cut!
I didn’t know how you’re playing this scene.
[SOMEONE IS WHINING NOW.]
I didn’t either. I didn’t see you.
I really had no idea how you portrayed it.
Me neither.
How did you play it?
I don’t know. I just played the song.
I was crying at the end.
[OHM MAKES IT VERY TOUCHING.]
It’s going to be the most impressive scene for me.
Turn the camera that way, please.
[OHM WAS COMPLETELY BLOCKED.]
And that was my seat.
Nanon was right there.
It was a very emotional scene.
Everything will be told in episode 11.
And we must link and connect the emotions.
But we didn’t get to see each other’s faces.
[P’YO IS SAYING THEY’RE PROFESSIONALS.]
I designed the act differently.
Whatever I felt during the song, I portrayed it that way.
And he acted his own way too.
I don’t know how they’re going to edit it
but P’Aof said we’re done filming for today.
Let’s see how it’s going to turn out.
I’m sure it will be one of the most impressive scenes.
I didn’t see you.
So I thought I’d think of all the flashbacks we had together.
I felt fulfilled.
Let’s see what P’Aof says.
Wait until they clear off this set.
Let’s go see him now.
It’s such a miracle.
They played it all from their imagination.
They were separated by a black partition.
But they did great.
P’Aof, was it really okay?
[HE’S STILL CURIOUS.]
What?
He was crying. Did I choose the right way to play it?
I do know how I’m going to edit the scene.
I just didn’t realize you wouldn’t get to see each other at all.
[THEY’RE TOTALLY BLOCKED.]
That black thing separated us.
Stay tuned, guys. You’ll love it.
Well, Pran was singing for his boyfriend.
Right.
This is P’Aof’s signature.
He did it before with P’Med scene (He’s Coming To Me).
Ohm played the whole scene by himself.
Exactly.
We’ll see how this one is going to turn out.
Have you ever watched The Wall Song?
They have to convey and link their feeling through the wall.
- Using their voices?
- Right.
Let’s see if we gave the right answer.
When you’re done here, go massage the guests over there.
They need foot massages.
[THE UNIFORM IS JUST RIGHT!]
Staff: Can you please take off the mic while giving an interview?
Of course!