中文（香港）字幕：@thai.monchi 有錯漏可以ig揾我
多謝 The Baker, Your Everyday Artisan Bakery.
大家好，歡迎嚟到 Arm Share
今集好特別
因為我哋嚟到好有愛嘅一個月
好似噉咁有愛
喺呢個咁正嘅moment
我邀請咗2位我好中意嘅弟弟上嚟
These two are lovey-dovey. They give us butterflies.
所以我想叫佢哋喺呢個咁特別嘅月份
We’ll have a mission for them too.
Before we get to the mission,
let’s meet them,
my beloved juniors–Ohm, Nanon.
Nanon, Ohm.
Sawasdee krub.
I called you in today because it’s a special occasion.
We are in the month of love, February.
So we have a couple…
from Bad Buddy Series that has just ended.
Yes.
It was very well received.
Thank you.
Tell us how you feel? You may thank your fans.
We are grateful to everyone who watches the series.
We feel that the hard work has paid off.
The dedication we put in over the past year has paid off.
Thank you very much for watching and giving us feedback,
and for loving this series.
We feel really happy.
Thank you so much.
Ohm agreed with everything his friend said.
That’s right.
Today, I have a mission for you two.
Okay.
It’s called the Secret Mission of Love.
I’m not gonna reveal it yet.
Tell you what? I have done many jobs before this.
And I’m a bit hungry right now.
An army marches on its stomach.
Right.
May I grab something to eat?
I’ve just looked at what I want to have.
You are hungry too, right?
And now, we are at The Baker.
The Baker is a premium bakery shop
located in Tops Market and Central Food Hall.
And its bakery products are Artisan bakeries.
They are just like homemade bakeries,
which are freshly baked and made with premium ingredients from around the world.
So the bakery products here have the taste and texture like those
from a premium bakery shop but at affordable prices.
These are European bakeries with an Asian twist.
Besides the great taste and quality ingredients,
they have Master Baker
who is a specialist with years of experience in baking.
Let me ask you this.
Do you two like bakeries?
Not so much.
MORE LIKE VERY MUCH HUNGRY
Just sometimes. I like to eat them when I have a chance to.
Is it good?
Yes. / Very much.
Let me tell you that the baked goods here at The Baker,
its Master Baker creates many types of baked goods that are fascinating
as he likes to pick up the trends from around the world to his creations.
His signatures with unique recipes are croissants and brioches.
Brioche is this one.
- This?
- Yes.
What is Brioche?
What is Brioche? I have someone who can give you an answer.
I don’t have specific knowledge of baking.
I have Master Baker who will tell you what Brioche is.
Let’s meet Master Baker.
All right.
And this is our Master Baker.
I have a question.
What is Brioche?
But there are many flavors in Brioche, right?
What flavor is this one?
This is Truffle Brioche.
Truffle?
Truffle from Italy.
There are many types here.
Let me sum up all the flavors they have.
This one is Candied Pecan Longan Honey Brioche.
It’s Brioche with Pecan and honey from longan flower.
And that one is Black Truffle.
And this one is French Butter Artisan Brioche.
These are the 3 favorite flavors from this bakery.
During this month of love,
Master Baker has created special baked products for Valentine's Day specifically.
It’s called Sweet Valentine L’Amour.
All the names are in Valentine's series.
They sound yum.
There are 5 types in the series.
All right, Master Baker has introduced his bakeries.
You two are hungry.
Why don’t you browse around and pick your favorites?
After that, I’ll bring you to the upper floor.
You two will have to create a special bakery.
You will get to learn it.
But now, I’ll let you choose your bakeries.
Can I have a croissant?
I’m gonna have this one.
Thank you.
Right now, we have chocolate and stuff for garnishing.
The creation today is…
Valentine L’Amour Chocolate Box from The Baker.
As you can see, there’s one finished product here.
I want to make one too.
But we don’t know how to decorate this yet.
Let Master Baker show us how to do it.
All right.
Please come in, Master Baker.
Hello again.
Sawasdee krub.
So L’amour means ‘Kwam Rak’.
Kwam Rak.
Let’s continue.
Okay. I’ll show you.
He’s drawing a heart over a heart-shaped cookie.
Next step is choosing the ingredients over here to decorate.
How did you do it, Ohm? Show it to the camera.
Right now, we are using 2 colors of chocolate icing to draw on the heart cookies.
and use them to decorate the chocolate box.
Have you two ever done something like this together?
No.
But I used to bake.
Really? You did it on your own account or for a show.
I did it on my own account.
Really? For what occasion?
For a birthday.
Okay. I’ve finished. I’m gonna put them in this.
In this chocolate box.
I have finished mine too. There are 5 pieces of cookies.
How is it going, Nanon?
It’s going well. I have finished 5 pieces.
Yeah!
Right now, the three of us have decorated these special chocolate items
made for Valentine’s Day.
And we have Master Baker to help us here.
Now, we will ask Master Baker to rate our work.
Let’s see how many scores we get.
Okay, Master Baker.
Give me the points from 1-10.
This one is mine.
6? Okay.
Give me more, please. Give me more.
No.
He’s so strict.
I wanna cry.
Okay, I got 6 points.
And this one?
6? Same score.
Last one.
Okay.
Arm got 6, Nanon got 6, and Ohm got 7 points.
All right. Thank you, Master Baker, for showing us how to make
and decorate these chocolate boxes.
Thank you so much.
Kids, thank Master Baker.
Thank you.
And these are the 3 Valentine’s L’Amour Chocolate Boxes from us.
Let’s check them out now.
This one is made by Ohm.
Why is there “NNN” inside the heart?
I made two pieces for Nanon.
There are several layers.
NNN is Nanon’s name.
Blue is the color of the Chelsea jersey.
Look, there’s Chelsea on this side.
Nanon likes Chelsea football club.
No.1 is the number of a goalkeeper.
The goalkeeper who gets No.1 is an excellent goalkeeper.
It’s Nanon’s favorite position in football.
Yes.
There are several layers to represent how good Nanon is at saving goals.
It has deep meaning.
And what is that?
I tried…
Joker?
I tried to draw Joker.
But it’s not close to it.
I made this to have the feel of a cartoon.
It looks like his face.
Big eyes with a cute tiny nose,
there it goes. It’s inside his mouth now.
As for my creation, I don’t have anyone so I made this for Arm Share.
For Arm Share fans.
Yes, for the fans of my show. Inside the box is my name.
And the word ‘Love’ here, so it is
Arm Love Arm Share.
We have finished our special sweet creations.
If you are looking for a special sweet bakery for Valentine’s Day,
come to The Baker between February 2 and 15.
This place can give you an experience that is beyond
and bring you premium delicacy at a good price.
It’s so convenient to shop at Tops Market and Central Food Hall
through 60 branches as well as online platforms,
www.tops.co.th and Grab application via GrabFood.
Not just that,
The Baker Thailand has another fun activity with Ohm and Nanon in this month of love.
When you buy any products from The Baker,
you’ll get a chance to win a video call with Ohm and Nanon.
See more details on how to join this activity on The Baker Thailand Facebook.
But today’s activity is not just making these chocolate boxes.
We have another mission which I already gave you homework.
If you have to dress each other
to look like a character from romantic movies,
which character do you like to dress your partner?
All right.
Have you picked a character yet?
I have.
Submit your homework to me now. What character do you want for Ohm ?
I want to dress Ohm as “Jack Dawson” from Titanic.
And what character do you give to Nanon?
I want him to be “Denchai” from Fan Day (One Day).
Okay. You did your homework. Very good.
Next, let’s go shopping and dress each other to the characters you have picked.
Let’s go.
Like I said I have a mission for you to do.
I want you to dress each other to a character in a romantic movie.
Why do you want to dress him as Jack Dawson?
I want him to drown to death.
Kidding.
- They are the Betadine Couple indeed.
- I don’t need to wear anything for that.
No. I feel that they share many of the same characteristics.
Jack in Titanic is bold and daring.
Jack wins a poker game, gets a Titanic ticket and jumps on the ship right away.
Once he sees the woman he likes, he just approaches her right away.
Ohm is like Jack in the movie.
If he’s Jack, then you have to pose in the nude for him to draw a sketch.
What do you want to dress him to?
Denchai from Fan Day.
Why?
Firstly, it’s a Thai film.
Secondly, Denchai cherishes love.
He can do anything for love.
Even though it’s wrong, he’s willing to do it.
Does he cherish you?
Hardly.
Show me.
What?
Don’t hurt him.
They are just teasing. It’s not that serious.
If you slap lightly on the skin, it’s not hurtful.
But if you slap with full force, it is hurtful.
That slap is just loud.
Earlier is just…
loud.
Just a sound.
Just on the surface.
But this…
No need to.
I brought you to Zara.
Please go shopping and find the clothes that match the character you chose.
Okay.
You can start browsing.
Take your time. Go.
Try wrapping around his neck and see if it works.
It works.
After this, we’ll take Nanon to get his hair permed to look like Denchai.
Do we need to go that far?
Assemble all pieces together and see how it goes.
1 outfit
Okay. How is Jack’s outfit going?
This is yours.
Just these two for Jack.
Jack will look like this.
Just add white suspenders then you are good to go.
And a white Tee.
A white Tee inside.
Try to place them on Denchai.
What about the top? Overcoat?
Topless.
No. I’m still looking for it. I haven’t found the one I like yet.
Apart from an overcoat, what is the inside layer?
A red shirt. I’m gonna pick that one, then.
Which one?
The problem is the outfit that Nanon has picked for Jack
has only 1 pair of pants left.
And the waist size is too large.
What is Ohm’s pants size?
Around 30
30 or 28.
28? He has such a tiny waist.
So you get only one?
Oh, there’s also a red shirt.
Yes. The red shirt.
Okay. Let’s pay for these first and go to another store.
All right. Let’s continue here, youngsters.
We haven’t gotten all the items we want yet.
We are now at PULL & BEAR.
You may continue.
Okay.
Hey.
Oh, he found it.
Camera, please zoom in to me.
Earlier, we called him here, right?
As he walked to here and waited for the cue,
he went, “Hey, this one works.”
“Yes. This is it.”
“Wait. Let them give us the cue first.”
What he acted earlier was so fake.
No, it was pretty smooth.
Was that smooth?
He did it smoothly. He was like…rolling eyes.
“Hey!”
I had an acting class.
Aof Nopphanarch’s pupil.
This one is perfect. I’m taking this one.
Great.
Get the correct size for Nanon.
XL?
It should be oversize. I want XXL.
XXL?
I’m gonna look for a shirt.
Instead of an overcoat. I’ll pick this one.
Ohm, what’s your pants size?
30?
I got these eyeglasses.
Denchai in the reference picture wears clear glasses.
But these are fashion glasses.
Nanon as Denchai is fashionable.
The boys have got outfits that match the characters in the movies they chose.
We are going to see
if the reference pictures we have and the outfits they bought
are similar or not.
How cute will they be?
I’ll take you to see them upstairs.
And right now, we are going to show you the main lead from Fan Day (One Day).
This is Denchai from the movie.
Let’s check out together if he looks like Denchai, a role of Ter Chantavit.
Please give it up for Denchai from Fan Day.
Ooh. It’s pretty cold, huh?
It’s freezing.
It’s freezing. Are you in a cold city?
As if I were in Hokkaido.
And this is Denchai from Fan Day.
It’s the character Ohm picked for Nanon to portray.
How do you feel?
I feel why the hell he picked this outfit for me.
While I chose a cool look for him.
How many percent do you think you look like Ter Chantavit?
Insert the reference picture on this side.
Next.
We have Jack from Titanic.
Let’s see if this interpretation of Jack can make Rose fall for him.
Let’s meet our Jack.
Why do you have to put on a cool face? I’m seriously curious.
Doesn’t it make you blush when he does that?
Hi, Jack.
Yo.
There’s “Yo” too.
What’s with the “Yo”? That’s not it.
Go talk to Jack.
Hello.
Sawasdee krub.
Oh, okay. Sawasdee krub.
What time in Thailand?
Do this. Like this.
My ship…
My ship has sailed.
And it’s Titanic too.
You got to dress as Jack picked by Nanon.
How do you feel?
At first, I didn’t think I could pull this off.
I thought it would be Oh!
You did. You actually pulled off this outfit.
Honestly. I picked his outfit too well.
He looks great on this.
He does.
Just like the handsome Jack Dawson.
Seriously.
He looks good too.
Don’t you agree?
He is handsome.
In a down-to-earth style.
He is handsome, seriously.
I’m not sure of it with this scarf on.
It’s cool on you.
Now they are fixing each other’s clothes.
You scared me.
That’s the look.
The audience can now vote.
If you like a Thai romantic film, vote 1 for Nanon.
If you like an international romantic film, vote 2.
Vote for Jack, write No.2.
Vote for Denchai, write No.1.
Now you all are dressed up.
I’ll take some pictures for you.
We look like the characters.
We do.
So we are wrapping up this episode with these two best friends
for this month of love.
We hope you all have a lovely relationship
like these two juniors of mine.
They agreed to join my show for this episode,
let’s thank them.
Thank you, Nanon. Thank you, Ohm.
Thank you.
We have to thank our kind sponsor too, The Baker, Your Everyday Artisan Bakery.
Thank you so much.
Us three, Arm, Ohm, and Nanon have to say Goodbye now.
Sawasdee krub.
I’m going with you.
Thank you, The Baker, Your Everyday Artisan Bakery.
Ohm, Nanon.
Hold on. Nanon enters first.
Welcome Nanon and Ohm.
Sawasdee krub.
What the?
You throw a gag right away?
He wanted to play this like what kids do.
You told me to do it.
No, I didn’t. I saw you folding a plane.
But the paper wasn’t made for it.
It’s the paper for bread and stuff.
Ah.
Here they go.
I can’t catch up with you guys.