This programme was filmed under strict COVID-19 preventive measures.
All the cast and crew members are vaccinated, and were tested with ATK before filming.
The filming began after everyone was tested negative.
That’s enough.
Hello!
Get to meet us every Saturday at 11 o’clock in this fun show…
School Rangers!
We welcome the new year with this new atmosphere, and more importantly.
See this?
A new uniform.
What do you guys think of the concept of this new uniform?
Higher-quality material.
Higher-quality material?
I think it’s more fashionable!
It looks extra.
We’re going into this new year with the bright red colour.
Red means we’re full of energy to bring happiness and entertainment to the fans.
WELL SAID
The uniform may be new. But we’ve still got all the rangers here, haven’t we?
ALL RANGERS PRESENT
We’re all here and we’ve got the same love and tenderness for each other, per usual.
Never have we ever thought of harming each other, again, per usual.
We’ve seen many of our rangers grow from when they first joined us.
Chimon, for example, joined the rangers when he was, what, 18-19?
Many of you have upped your skills.
You weren’t so eloquent before but now y’all talk loads.
Like P’White, who was shy and calm, is now hilarious.
P’White is now rough and brave.
P’White is now full of jokes.
That’s enough.
NO NEED FOR FLATTERY
When we started out, P’Arm always won every game like the perfect man that he was.
But lately? Not so much.
ARM HAS LEO’S HEAD MARKED
We’ll see about that.
Has time been cruel to you, P’Arm?
Let’s not talk about that.
If we’re talking about development, mine lies in my ability to host live events.
I used to go with P’Leo and Godji, right?
Now they only need me and Godji. P’Leo isn’t necessary.
HARSH!
Someone with your demeanour needs to take an intensive course.
This is in order for you to become a proper ranger.
So I’ve got a special course just for you, Leo!
But really, when it comes to fighting spirit, I’m proud of everyone here.
Now, whichever show our rangers join, they always fight to the death.
Everyone here is much stronger.
EVOLUTION
To conclude, we have evolved so much over 200 episodes.
And our love for each other has also grown.
But today, we’ll be joined by three more rangers.
NEW FRIENDS
We’ve got 12 rangers right now, but three more are joining?
Not one member left, and three more are joining!
THIS GETS REALLY COSY
Please welcome the first new ranger, Earth Pirapat!
Get on, everyone!
HE GIVES IT HIS ALL
Y’all made me do that first thing in the show?
Aren’t ya fit for your first episode?
Leave it to me to go big.
Are you really going to park it right here?
Earth made such a cool entrance.
But the next guy will make an elegant entrance.
WHO?
Please welcome Mix Sahaphap!
Hi there, Mix.
Not that. He’s over here!
Hello.
He did make an elegant entrance.
He’s literally promoting his hometown.
Welcome to my team.
But we’ve still got one more. Who’s the next guy, Tay Tawan?
These two made such cool entrances, but they don’t measure up to the last guy.
EXPECT A GRAND ENTRANCE
Please welcome First Kanaphan!
WHERE IS HE COMING FROM?
Is he entering from up above?
Where is he?
He’s coming!
HE’S HERE
I’m here!
How the hell does this thing even work!
First Kanaphan!
Hello.
They asked you to ride that from over there?
Yeah.
But you just carried it.
It’s hard to ride.
You turned the wheel the wrong way.
Then how should I do it?
This side turns forward, not the other way around.
Go back and start over.
I’m begging you.
I was waiting so long to make an entrance.
It’s for entertainment.
Just do as your seniors ask, man!
Yes, sir!
OBEDIENT
Too far, man.
Now that’s the correct way.
Steer harder.
AS REQUESTED
That was the ranger spirit!
So we’ve got three more friends this year.
Earth Pirapat, Mix Sahaphap, and First Kanaphan.
The three upcoming stars are full of all-rounded potentials.
First was formerly a school idol, but now he’s an upbeat school ranger.
Earth has devoted his life to school rangers.
With his titan build, he’s been asked to go on various missions for school rangers.
The energetic guest star has now joined the show as a formidable ranger.
Lastly, Mix, the guest star who may not win the game, but win fans’ hearts.
Now he’s ready to win the hearts of people as the new ranger.
To perfectly welcome the new year, not only do we have three new members,
we have also upgraded our uniforms, too!
With new rangers and new uniforms, the new episodes will be even more fun.
Stay tuned to School Rangers 2022!
Since the new members are here for the first time as rangers, let them officially introduce themselves.
Hello. I’m Earth, your new ranger!
Hi there!
I’m First Kanaphan Puitrakul, also a new ranger. I’ll be in your care!
Hello. I’m Mix Sahaphap, the newest ranger.
These three have appeared in our show as guests.
But now that they’re here as rangers, do you guys know what qualifications must rangers have?
Strength and speed.
I think the key attribute of a school ranger host, which is most important…
is looks.
GOOD ONE
Not only looks, but also skills.
The ability to compete.
The strength.
The brain.
These are the things I… don’t have.
But I hope this show will help me fulfil them.
Slowly learning to get better.
Like what my friend said, we need looks.
Don’t believe everything you hear.
Go on.
Well, I don’t have any of those, either.
The skills, like First said, I’ll get from this show.
As seniors, we’ll give you newbies an orientation.
We have actually done a workshop to get familiar with each other.
If you’d like to know how chaotic that workshop was, take a look.
How did the orientation of the new rangers go?
Let’s see after a short commercial break.
Sponsored by Doi Kham’s tomato products.
We’re back with School Rangers: Intro to Rangers!
With new members joining,
we have a prep battle for the rangers to practice and get familiar with each other.
Form a circle, please.
Form a circle.
ORIENTATION
LET’S GO
Spread the circle out, guys.
GREEN NITIWAT TANTIPATSIRI
Green		We’ll be playing this game called Hu-Ha-Hi. Say it, Hu-Ha-Hi!
Hu-Ha-Hi.
Hu-Ha-Hi!
This game will heighten your senses.
A good MC needs their senses. Repeat after me. Eyes on.
Eyes on!
You need your eyes always open.
Ears on.
Ears on!
Good job, children.
Sound on.
Sound on!
Body on.
Body on!
Lastly, mind on. Your mind needs to be alert.
Alright? Put your hands into a gun.
WELL ARMED
This is what we’re gonna do.
One of us will say “Hu” and shoot upward. Say it with me. Hu!
Hu!
Shoot your gun upward. Hu!
Only one person at a time. For example, if I go “Hu!”
The guys next to me need to turn their awareness on.
Keep yourself aware. If one person goes “Hu”, the guys next to them go “Ha” with a swing.
Let’s try in 1, 2, 3, Hu!
THERE THEY GO
Then you can look for your next target.
If I shoot at Sing.
Hu!
The two right next to him go “Ha!”
Now Sing shoots at the next target.
Keep your eye contact game strong.
You guys are MCs of the same show, you need to be clear who you’re looking at.
If you’re slow, they’ll all know.
We’ll eliminate those who make mistakes one by one until there’s only one man left.
What a fun game this is. Applaud!
Spread the circle out far and wide, guys.
START!
SLOWLY
Hu!
Ha!
Hi!
Hu!
FOCUS
WHITE OUT!
You lost!
The first one to be eliminated is White.
It’s alright.
Wait on the sideline, White.
Go away, man.
DON’T FIGHT, GUYS
You’re so mean, P’Nicky.
Wait, what?
That’s “Ha”, you need to go “Hi”.
Oh, dang! Nicky was a little overexcited that he popped his pants so wide.
And these are Dior!
They’re not used to strenuous work, huh?
I’m so bummed.
That was a good joke, though unintentional, please give Nicky a hand!
POOR GUY
ELIMINATED ONE BY ONE
MOND DID NOT MAKE IT
Be focused, guys.
Hahu!
Oh, Gun.
BY A SYLLABLE
There they are, eliminated one by one.
This game really requires total concentration and wits.
The perfect way to train the rangers.
ELIMINATED
Aren’t they both new members?
Yes.
Stand back to back.
We’ll give them a topic.
For example, which animals are land animals.
If it is a land animal, the two guys here take a step forward.
You guys will be the ones coming up with ideas, like a horse.
Since horse is a land animal, these two take a step. A cow. That’s another step.
But if someone says an aquatic animal or any non-land animal.
What they need to do is to turn around and shoot the other guy.
Whoever shoots first wins.
You guys come up with a topic.
Let’s do provinces. Should be easy enough.
So the deciding moment is when it’s not a province in Thailand.
Get ready. Close your eyes, you two.
If you have an idea, raise your hand and I’ll point at you.
Bangkok.
CORRECT
Saraburi.
Prachinburi.
Is that a province?
Pattaya.
HESITATING
Pattaya isn’t a province.
Let’s think they’re even.
MIX IS CONFUSED
Khon Kaen.
Who else?
Chonburi.
Hatyai.
Bang!
And the winner is First!
HE’S GOOD
Hatyai isn’t a province, guys.
They shouldn’t have come this far.
It’s a district.
This should have ended with Pattaya.
Give the winner a round of applause.
THANK YOU
They really do try their best to learn about and bond with the new members.
Although Off and Gun must leave for work before this is over, the orientation goes on.
Let’s see what other skill set they’re acquiring.
This team is the red team and this is the blue.
You’ll be given a rough script and have two minutes to prepare.
Let’s begin.
You’re free to rehearse right now.
Now it is time for them to design their own style as MCs.
Both teams are so determined.
Try not to be reading the lines.
Feel free to add more to the story, but make sure you get the ideas across.
Please welcome the first team.
This way, gentlemen.
You guys who are watching, try not to laugh at their jokes.
PATIENT
You have five minutes.
Ready? In 5, 4, 3, 2…
Hello!
Oi, that’s the wrong way!
THEY AIM FOR LAUGHTERS
Somebody's already laughing.
CAN’T HOLD BACK
This week on School Rangers, the rangers are visiting Khao Kheow Open Zoo!
FULL OF ENERGY
Why Open Zoo Khao Kheow?
Well, how would you get in if they’re a “Close” Zoo?
MORE JOKES
We’re here to see various animals.
Such as a hippo.
Moo!
ARE YOU SURE?
A giraffe!
A snake!
A monkey!
A fox!
We’re also here to admire the good work of the students around here
with this “Finish the Proverb” game.
Are you guys familiar with proverbs?
Yes.
Really?
LET’S TEST
Make hay while…?
While the sun shines.
And if the sun doesn’t shine?
Don’t make any hay.
WHAT PROVERB IS THIS
You’ve got a problem with my jokes?
These are high quality jokes.
GOOD JOB
This team is led by Big Brother Nicky so it’s guaranteed to be funny.
They sure get a lot of laughter from the other team.
Now let’s see what Big Brother Leo’s team got up their sleeves.
Ready? Go!
1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, Hey!
If you’re happy and you know it, clap your hands!
You’ve successfully wasted one minute.
HE KNOWS
Hello!
School Rangers this weekday.
Weekend!
This weekend is very special.
How special is that?
Very very special.
Because the rangers are on a field trip today.
We came up with the same joke as them but we’re allowed to just tell it again.
The animals are king kong!
GO BIG
A woodpecker!
GO BIGGER
A bull!
HE FORGOT
What did we assign you as again?
A tiger.
HE FORGOT
NO HOLDING BACK
What about you?
Me?
I’m a polar bear.
Lots of animals.
Not only will we meet these animals, but we’re admiring the good work of the students from around here.
To play our game, the players must imitate animals to complete the mission.
WELL DELIVERED
Stay tuned to the special episode of School Rangers: Zoo Rangers!
Okay!
Alright, alright! Both teams are doing well in the prep battle.
The workshop went well without a hitch. But how will they do in the real battleground?
Come back in the next break!
Time to officially welcome the three new members to the bunch.
What they did in the workshop is merely child play.
The real deal is waiting up ahead.
But for now, it is time to pick their team members!
Feel free to boast your skill sets, boys!
Alright, we’re now done with our workshop.
But what we need as a ranger is, first, wit.
Second, strength.
Third, we need teamwork.
And fourth, versatility.
So besides the workshop, we will be working on these skills
to get the new members more familiar with them.
Then we should ask the new rangers.
Versatile, witty, and good at teamwork.
I’ve got it all.
So cool.
It’s my first episode, after all.
I have to boast a little.
What about you, P’Mix?
Me? I think I’m very nimble.
You tripped over yourself just this morning, dude.
TOO NIMBLE, PERHAPS
I think what stands out about me is my wit.
I don’t have the strength to go against the muscly guys, honestly.
But I don’t know if I can have good teamwork with y’all, though, since this is my first episode.
We’ll have to wait and see about that.
Wait, wait. What’s with the serious outlook?
Gotta boast a little.
Just remember what you guys said today.
When you reach a hundred episodes, it won’t be like this.
WORDS OF ADVICE
Of course, what’s really fun about School Rangers isn’t only the games,
but also the spirit to fight to the death of us rangers.
Because our penalties are really brutal.
I get it.
You do?
I get the penalty every time I come here.
And what’s really gonna save you from the possibility of these penalties is none other than having a strong team.
IMPORTANT
So we’re going to get into teams today.
We’ve got 15 rangers right now.
That means the rangers will be divided into three teams with five people each.
As a welcome gift to the rookies, they’ll be the ones choosing the members.
INTERESTING
We will decide who chooses first at random.
You will pick your team members one by one.
Who do you guys want, or not want, in your team and why?
I’m not very careful.
I’m the type to recklessly blast my way through.
So you’re gonna choose me?
THE VERY CAUTIOUS TAY
Who’re you gonna choose? Arm?
THE RIGHT GUY
P’Arm is very analytical and careful.
ANALYTICAL AND CAREFUL
So that’s why.
Then who is it that you absolutely don’t want on your team?
That’s hard.
Let’s move on to Mix.
TRIES TO CHANGE THE SUBJECT
I don’t want him to say it’s me he doesn’t want.
Who is it that you don’t want?
I can’t answer that.
No need to feel intimidated. We’re brothers.
Who is it?
Don’t freaking look at me.
DON’T PICK HIM
Who is it?
AVOIDING EYE CONTACT
Mr Tay Tawan is avoiding all eye contact right now.
NOT SO LOUD, MOND
No, he’s like my brother, so I’m okay with him.
PHEW!
Relieved, aren’t you?
Just say it, Earth. There are no hard feelings after this.
It’s probably Mond.
He and I are both brawny so we’re bound to become careless.
I don’t want our recklessness off the chart.
REASONABLE
THEY’RE BOTH ENERGETIC
Too powerful, right?
What about you, Mix?
Actually, there are two guys I want on my team.
First is P’Arm.
Another is P’Gun.
And you called me your freaking idol, traitor.
UH-OH!
You really are my idol!
SOMEONE IS HOLDING A GRUDGE
P’Arm is sensible.
Like P’Earth said, he could be keeping us on the ground since he’s careful.
I’ve played with P’Gun before.
He’s got leadership.
With him on the team, we’re definitely gonna win.
And who is a no-no? Who is it that you can’t have on your team?
P’Tay.
AS EXPECTED
He didn’t even have to think about it.
He meant every word.
No, P’Tay and I are too alike.
Two of the same sort can’t be on the same ship.
We’re bound to wreck.
What sort are we?
The clumsy sort.
THEY’RE BOTH CLUMSY
What about you, First? Who do you want on your team?
I’ve got two on my mind.
P’Nicky and P’Leo.
THE BIG BROTHERS
I want someone sluggish to keep me in check.
I’m moving too fast.
Someone what again?
Sluggish and compliant.
If you don’t pick any of us as your first teammate, man.
Sure. I want someone sluggish and compliant to keep me in check.
Did you say compliant?
I did, compliant.
I get the sluggish part, but complaint sounds a little unusual.
So you want someone to slow you down.
He wants a veteran.
And who is it that you don’t want?
I don’t want P’Tay.
Why?
Because he and I are both chatty.
You’re afraid he’ll out-chat you.
You’re on the same wavelength.
We’re on the same wavelength.
HOW MEAN OF YOU, BROTHER
Alright, now we know who they want and who they don’t want.
The most popular choice is Arm.
And the least popular choice is Tay.
MEANIE
May luck be with you, rookies, because it’s time to choose. Let’s begin.
Ones-and-twos
The first one.
MIX IS THE FIRST ONE OUT.
He will be the last one to pick.
BUMMER!
Rock, paper, scissors.
Earth will be the first one to pick the members,
followed by First and Mix is the last one.
The first member that you want to join your team.
Earlier, you said that you want Arm.
Yes.
Now you get the chance to choose. Will you pick Arm?
Your first member.Who will you choose, Earth?
I’ll pick my brother.
Me?
What about Arm?
Next round.
I’m nervous.
Why?
I never thought he would pick me because he didn’t choose me earlier.
Right?
He also talked about your bad bone.
Yes.
I’m kind-hearted. I think Off…
No one will pick me.
Yes.
HE LOVES HIS BROTHER.
Thank you.
You chose him out of pity.
You are kind-hearted.
Okay, next person.
First.
Who will you choose?
P’ Leo
Do I have any other choice?
FEEL SO PRESSURED!
TRY TO BE COMPOSED.
WHY ARE YOU SMILING?
I choose P’ Gun.
Why did you take him away from me?
SAME CHOICE.
Because Gun has what I don’t have.
What is it?
He’s not afraid of height.
HE KNOWS THAT TOO.
I’m afraid of height.
FILL IN HIS WEAK POINT.
Mix, who will you choose?
Tay?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
He doesn’t even look this way.
PLEASE LOOK THIS WAY.
Like you’ve said, this side is not even in his sight.
Do you know that Sing is also one of the rangers?
I plan to choose P’ Sing and P’ Mond.
Will you choose them?
I’m not surprised that you want to choose Mond.
But I’m surprised that you want to choose me.
I played a game with you once.
You were agile.
HE’S RELIEVED.
So your first pick is…?
P’ White.
AN UNEXPECTED CHOICE.
HE IS A TOUGH GUY.
Congrats, bro.
He finally gets chosen.
Based on your choice, I guess you didn’t watch this show much.
Next, Earth. Who will you choose to be the second member of your team?
P’ Arm WC.
THE ACE.
He’s an intimidating choice.
IMPROVE HIS STRENGTH.
I’m ready to win.
First.
I’ll choose an ace, P’ Nicky.
AS PROMISED.
Who did you choose earlier?
P’ Nicky, P’ Gun, and me.
HE LOVES THE TEAM.
P’ Tay.
REALLY?!
THEIR LUCKS ARE NOW CONNECTED.
I want to beat the curse of this show.
Back to Earth. Who will you choose to be your third member?
Analyze your choice first.
I want to break the rule of this show.
AGAIN?!
HOW?
Newie.
ANOTHER TOUGH GUY.
This team is scary.
TOUGH TEAM.
Who is on the team?
Earth, New, and Arm.
First, you can choose anyone but Leo.
PLEASE CHOOSE ME.
Pick him.
I don’t want to be in First’s team.
No, choose the person next to him.
P’ Leo.
THIS WOULD BE FUN.
I’m afraid that the three teams wouldn’t be balanced.
First!
It’s me.
Did you forget me?
First, Leo is a terrible choice.
I think we need an ace in our team.
Yes, we need one.
WHO IS HE?
Someone talented, fast, agile, and always won games.
HE MUST BE VERY TALENTED.
P’ Sing.
HE CAN’T BELIEVE HIS EARS.
Look at his face.
Good choice.
Now, I believe that you have never watched School Rangers.
THESE ARE ALL THE ACES.
We will end the curse.
HE HAS HIS GOAL.
This is a new era.
Just like soccer, this is the start of a new season.
Forget all the past.
Since we already come this way, I will choose…
DON’T CHOOSE ANOTHER TOUGH GUY.
WHO WILL IT BE?
I choose Mond.
ANOTHER TOUGH GUY.
I think my team is lack of strength.
In terms of strength, it’s going to be Chimon or Nanon.
I choose Nanon.
You never watched this show!
THIS WOULD BE FUN.
Nanon is worse than Leo and me.
His body is big. He must have some strength.
HE FOCUSES ON THE SIZE.
He still can’t find his strong point.
Who will you choose?
I intend to choose Chimon.
Let’s go to the extreme and begin a new era.
I want to see Mix’s team standing together the most.
Let’s stand with our teams.
After we have selected our teams,
I’ll give each team to talk about what is in their mind.
For Team A, let’s start with Gun.
I’m very happy that we have a chance to join a talk…
HE MUST BE SO EXCITED THAT HIS TONGUE GETS TWISTED.
A team.
…join the team with familiar faces such as P’ Leo and P’ Nicky.
HE MUST BE SO EXCITED THAT HIS TONGUE GETS TWISTED.
A team.
…join the team with familiar faces such as P’ Leo and P’ Nicky.
But you looked devastated earlier.
If we watch the moment that First said my name, Gun was totally devastated.
P’ Leo.
First!
I don’t want to be punished.
It’s me.
That’s not true.
Why?	How was it?
It was great. I just couldn’t believe that First would pick you.
HOW SHOULD I MAKE AN EXCUSE FOR THIS?
It was unbelievable.
We were happy.
THAT’S WHAT HAPPENED.
You didn’t do it because you were unhappy.
HE WAS HAPPY.
What about when he picked me?
I’m very happy.
His eyes are lying.
Since we are in the same team today, we will go through it together.
HE ENDS IT ON A HIGH NOTE.
What about Team B?
Tell them, P’ Tay.
It’s destiny that brings us together.
You are all in Team B?
TEAM B GANG?
Your team looks quite worrisome.
Our team is quite talented.
You should worry about your team first.
THE KID TALKS BACK.
But Team C looks like they are not afraid of anything.
Look at their members.
They look like a tank.
THE TEAM IS FULL OF POWER.
Arm, you are standing like you are already the winner.
What about this, combine Team A and B to compete against Team C?
We are not that good.
DON’T GANG UP ON US.
I’m afraid that you still defeat us anyway.
LET’S FIGHT, SHALL WE?
If Team C is defeated today, the other two teams will be extremely happy.
LET’S WAIT AND SEE.
When we set up our teams and this filming is over, you will say that this is unexpected.
I WANT TO SAY IT NOW!
Team C, how do you feel?
I’m glad that he picked me first.
Because I’m already a part of his team.
I saw him adding more weapons to the team.
HE PLANNED IT WELL.
I felt that our team is special.
Full of aces.
WE ARE ALL ACES.
Right.
We need to name our teams, right?
That’s a must.
LET’S NAME OUR TEAMS.
Let’s start with Team C.
The names of the teams need to be based on animal names.
Bantam.
Team B, what’s your team’s name?
Our team’s name…
LET’S DISCUSS FIRST.
If a rat fights, can you handle it? (Noo in Thai can mean both ‘a rat’ and ‘I’)
The rat won’t lose.
We have Bantam and Rat. What about the last team?
Our team’s name comes from a frightening animal.
Spider.
What kind of spider?
Tarantula.
What do you hunt?
Let’s say goodbye for now. (La means ‘hunt’ and ‘goodbye’ in Thai)
THEY ARE PLAYING A EASY JOKE.
UNEXPECTED.
He helped open the joke.
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
Three jokes.
HE IS SO PROUD.
Now the teams have been divided.
Their verbal skill is not worrisome.
What about their ability? Let’s see it in the next break.
Let’s go. It’s time for all the 15 rangers to do a mission together for the first time.
The new rangers have joined us in several missions as guests.
Will they be able to write a new history as they take on a new role?
Let’s check it out.
This mission is about agility.
Agility can be crucial quality to help you win in certain types of games.
Talking about agility, Leo…
Yes.
He’s the worst.
The person who is good at it is Gun, Arm, and Chimon.
Me, too.
DON’T FORGET ME.
Mix, you too?
I’m agile.
Let’s give him a try.
WAIT AND SEE.
He’s there.
Gun and Chimon, can you tell us your secrets for agility?
I’m not sure if I have a secret for it.
When I play a game, I just want to finish it as fast as I can.
FOCUS ON THE GOAL.
I’m petit.
So I can move fast.
Are you afraid that you might fall down when you are in a high place?
No because I know that there are safety gears.
HE FEELS ASSURED.
What if there’s no safety gear?
I will be afraid.
Why did you ask that?
SO WHAT?
Arm, what is your secret?
I have no secret as well. This is a gifted talent.
Even though we all do our best, the results are still different.
HE IS RIGHT.
Then we don’t need to ask Chimon, do we?
Let’s ask him.
I just do my best. Work as hard as I can.
I will do my best because I want to beat this team.
A BIG OPPONENT.
Why does it have to be my team?
Your team looks strong and all-rounded.
I saw Earth’s skills when we filmed the Boy Scout episodes.
Why?
You are just big.
Really?
But you were weak.
That was my acting.
You were weak and clumsie.
HIS TONGUE GETS TWISTED.
Let’s see this time.
Don’t judge me yet.
How will agility play a role in the first game?
Let’s see the rule of the game.
The rule of ‘The Higher, The Better’ game.
Each team will send one of its members to play the game in each round.
The players will use their agility to walk on a wobbly bridge.
They will use their head and knee to hit all the balloons along the course.
There are two rounds for this game.
Based on their total time record, each
team will receive 3, 2, and 1 point respectively.
I have never seen it before.
YOUR ACTING LOOKS SO NATURAL.
I look this way so I didn’t see it.
UNBELIEVABLE.
I’ve never seen it before.
This game is not hard for me at all.
I did it in the Powerful Hip game.
P’ Leo, Nonon, P’ Gun, Sing, and I had played the game.
I’m the best at using my hip
I’m the best in the field.
If I have to boast about it.
Leo
Yes.
He used to be good at it.
He was shrugging.
He’s getting older so he…
I’M SAD.
But his physical condition is not good now.
I’m not as agile as I used to be but now I start to feel angry at you.
HE HITS BACK.
See? He can make them rhyme.
The new rangers - First, Mix and Earth, will compete in the first round.
In the second round, each team can choose their player.
Gun from Team A raises his hand.
Team B sends Sing to compete in the game.
Team C gives the duty to Arm.
Based on the player, it will be a close game.
Team B, why do you send Sing to play the game?
The other members have drama filming schedules.
Sing doesn’t have a schedule for tomorrow.
I mean nothing to you.
HE LOVES HIS BRO.
If you get injured, it won’t affect your schedule.
I can get injured.
You can get injured.
But I won’t let my feelings get hurt.
How is my rhyme?
THE KID IS FIGHTING BACK.
When this team sends Sing, my team feels sorry (pun jokes).
THAT’S TOO INSULTING.
Rock, paper, scissors.
We won.
THEY WILL BE THE LAST TEAM TO PLAY.
You can observe the first team and it won’t feel so pressured since we are not the last to play.
Okay.
Team B will be the first to play.
Team A will go second.
Team C will be the last.
Let’s go.
How is it up there?
LET’S CHECK HIS CONDITION.
At first, it doesn’t look scary.
What about now?
I’m so scared.
HE IS IN TROUBLE.
Don’t try to scare my team.
It’s okay. If you fall down, I’ll catch you.
I’M READY TO CATCH YOU.
I don’t believe you.
You don’t need to hurry because First is scared of height.
HE KNOWS MY WEAKNESS.
First, you will lose this game.
You do it well first.
Mix, fighting!
We need to cheer on him. So he won’t be afraid.
It’s like we are there to catch him.
I’m afraid that he will fall on us.
Don’t be afraid.
Hurry up.
Easy. Be careful.
AFRAID BUT NOT GIVE UP.
We are here to catch you.
TAY TAWAN, THE CHEERLEADER.
READY TO CATCH HIM.
OH!?
His first few steps look fine. Then, he almost falls down.
HIS HEART SKIPS A BEAT.
KEEP GOING. DON’T STOP.
TAKE A BREAK.
What is he going to do?
Will he keep going or quit?
He needs to make the decision quickly as the clock is ticking.
MIX, FIGHT ON!
I’M AFRAID FOR HIM.
I hope First won’t be too afraid after watching his friend playing the game.
HE KEEPS WATCHING MIX.
Be brave.
Mix, keep going.
Take it easy.
HE HAS A FIGHTING SPIRIT.
WOBBLY.
The gold is waiting for you.
HIS CHEERING IS NON-SENSE.
Mix, fight on.
White, go and cheer on him.
NOT FAR TO THE FINISH LINE.
HE SCREAMS TO BEAT HIS FEAR.
Scream out loud.
RELEASE YOUR ENERGY.
Team C is secretly practicing their moves.
ALMOST THERE.
THE LAST THREE BALLOONS.
Above you.
I SURVIVED.
Mix, you are great.
That’s unexpected.
Superb.
That was fast.
My legs are shaking.
His legs are already shaking because he’s afraid of height.
HIS LEGS ARE NOT COOPERATING WITH HIM.
We are in trouble.
It’s okay, First. This is nothing.
Don’t look down.
TRY TO COMFORT HIM.
It’s super scary. It’s really high.
The planks are wobbly.
I need to find my balance first.
If I’m not careful, I can fall down.
HE’S STILL TIRED.
My legs were shaking.
I was so scared.
I did it quickly because P’ Boy told me if I win the game, I will get additional money.
HE FOUGHT FOR THE PRIZE.
His strong point was that he screamed to relieve his stress.
He did it well from the first to the last screams.
If he fell down, we would run away from there.
Then I would run back to help him after he landed on the ground.
You are such a terrible friend.
I’m sure I can beat First.
LET’S WAIT AND SEE.
The picture I had in my head vs. reality.
It’s scarier?
It’s scarier than I thought.
These two big bros will send moral support to you
First – my friend, it’s okay.
I passed it.
Be careful not to fall down.
Relax, First. Nothing is higher than our heart.
I showed you how to do it. Now you know what to do.
My anger spikes up.
Wait and see.
I’ll wait and see.
CALM DOWN, BRO.
Wait and see.
You haven’t shown your physical skill but your verbal skill is second to none.
Take it easy.
Take step by step.
SLOW BUT SECURE.
Keep going.
Left and right.
That’s pretty fast.
HE’S EXCITED.
Keep going.
THE CROWD IS VERY EXCITED.
First, be careful.
First is trying to stay calm to beat his fear.
While his teammates seem to be more excited than him.
First, you are doing well.
THEY ARE SO LOUD.
STUDY THE OPPONENT.
Team C is quiet observing him,
Are they feeling nervous or are they planning something?
Take it easy.
ALMOST THERE.
HE’S LOWERING HIS BODY.
He uses this technique.
HERE COMES THE DOUBLE-KNEE STRIKE.
FIGHT ON, BRO.
He’s pretty fast.
HE IS SPEEDING UP.
HE STARTS TO WORRY.
Between him and me, who is faster?
THE SHAPE OF HIS LIPS SAYS EVERYTHING.
Between First and me, who is faster?
Pretty much the same.
HE IS CHANGING HIS RESPONSE.
IT ALMOST ENDS.
JUST ONE MORE STEP.
Unlike me, he doesn’t waste any time when piercing the balloons.
Heading.
HE IS ROOTING FOR FIRST.
It’s the last balloon. First, hurry up and end the game.
WELL DONE.
It’s not that scary.
That was fast, bro.
It wasn’t as scary as I had thought.
NOW HE BECOMES VERY VOCAL.
Why did you take so long?
I missed the ballons.
First, you were so fast.
I like this technique of you.
I LOVE IT.
That was very fast.
It’s okay. We still have Sing.
The soldier doesn’t end, don’t count the war.
The war hasn’t ended.
It wasn’t that scary.
Was I fast? I think I was pretty fast.
HE RETURNS TO HIGH SPIRITS NOW.
This is a hidden gift inside me.
I think it’s great that I found a new talent in the game.
Can you tell us your true feeling?
My legs were shaking since the first step.
Why didn’t you scream?
I was too afraid to scream.
During the game, it was scary.
But it was scarier when I climbed down.
First did very well from observing Mix.
Mix was quite slow and took a long time to finish.
From my observation, First was much faster.
He might be faster than me.
At first, I thought you would be slower than Mix.
But when you did it, you had your rhythm and barely made any mistake.
LET’S PRAISE HIM.
Now is time for the last team of this round.
After studying the game for a while, Earth, it’s time to show your skill.
Did you see examples from the two previous players?
Yes.
Those are amateurs.
But you are…
…a bunch. (pun jokes on Thai words)
I can say I’m second to none.
TOTALLY CONFIDENT.
Listen here. Someone wants to say something to you.
You can do it.
MORAL SUPPORT.
Thank you.
He didn’t know it was our plan.
But he gains strength from it.
Then our plan went wrong.
Will Tay’s plan to falsely praise Earth work?
Let’s see.
Go. Keep going.
The game is over.
SUPER FAST.
ARE YOU IN A RUSH?
Tay’s plan doesn’t work with Earth.
He is unstoppable and as fast as lightning.
HE DOESN’T MAKE A SINGLE MISTAKE.
SUPER SCARY.
He’s very fast.
HE’S THE REAL DEAL.
Take it easy, Earth.
WHY IS HE SO FAST?
WHAT WAS YOUR PLAN?
THE PLAN FAILS.
HE IS SO CHILL.
Earth is going forwards at a fast speed.
He’s not afraid nor stoppable.
He’s too strong.
THEY FEEL RELAXED NOW.
Pierce it. Left and right.
HE’S NOT SLOWING DOWN AT ALL.
EARTH IS COMING.
AMAZING.
GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
SO PROUD.
Your plan to cheer for him.
The plan went wrong.
Let’s get him some support so he would be overconfident.
But he did so well.
THANK YOU, BUDDY.
Did you see it?
It’s like we already won since the first round.
I’m not here to lose. I’m here to win.
I’M SERIOUS.
You kept stepping forward nonstop.
Yes, but deep down, I was nervous.
But I only thought I had to do it faster than the other two teams.
Were your scared/
I’m not afraid of height.
First was wrong. This time I won’t take it easy on him.
I’M HERE TO WIN.
Let’s give Earth round applause.
First was wrong. This time I won’t take it easy on him.
THE PRIDE OF THE TEAM.
Let’s give Earth round applause.
How was I?
You were very fast. I thought you were the god of thunder.
He made me unexpectedly proud.
I thought he would be hasty.
But he wasn’t at all.
There is a jealous team next to us.
DON’T SHOW IT.
Where?
This is easy.
The next round will be easy too.
Yes, if Sing starts the game.
But I’m worried about Gun.
Gun will be fast.
Don’t say you are worried. Say you are afraid.
IS IT THAT BAD?
When it comes to speed, he is no.1.
This fun in this week is over.
But don’t be so quick to judge.
It’s not certain who will win the game.
The first round allows the three new
rangers – First, Earth, and Mix to show their potential.
They all have fighting spirits.
They will be able to compete with the veteran rangers just fine.
How will the result of this game turn out? Check it out next week.
Thank you, the Verona at Tab Lan in Prachinburi, for the filming location.
It’s close to Bangkok, with only 2-3 hours of driving.
The air is fresh and the accommodations are comfortable.
It’s a great place for a family vacation.
If you are an adventure lover, there are many obstacles for you to enjoy.
There’s also a flower garden for photo shooting.
Thank you.
The players in the second round are also as good as those in the first round.
Who will win the first game?
Find out in the next episode, airing next Saturday at noon.