Leo, give them a signal.
Since we don’t want to make this year’s first punishment too bitter,
we are going to soak them with sweeten-flavored water.
We hope sweetness can help conquer your bitterness.
White, are you going to take revenge on me?
Dude, this is filled with my love.
WITH LOVE AND RED DRINK!!
Tay doesn’t allow us to punish.
Be ready.
One, two, three!
Go!
Well, they’re no longer brothers for now, are they?
WHAT A REFRESHING SWEETNESS!!
We have this horror movie scene here.
He is soaked.
White and Chimon are not in a pleasant condition now.
I HAD BETTER RUN!!
We also have an action movie scene around here.
Who wants to get soaked alone, huh?
Ready and go!!
It’s alright.
Well, how come there’s a romantic scene here?
That’s a gentle punishment.
What a sweet one, Mix.
Wash your face.
SHAKING TO DEATH!!
Freezing!
Come on.	Losers must take care of themselves.
CLINGING SO TIGHTLY!
Hey, please give elephants those drinks.
He wants to get washed.
I feel like I also get punished,
THAT’S CALLED LOVE!!
This is our perfect ending of School Rangers: ‘Intro to Rangers’.
In addition to using different skills in competing,
our rangers have also learned to accept both victory and failure.
Fight on, our 15 rangers!
Great, Best, Amazing!	Our rangers!
It’s a wrap for School Rangers’ special episode, ‘Intro to Rangers.’
After we got our basic skills adjusted,
I want to ask our three new rangers.
Which skill do you think you are good at?
I think I’m agile, quick, and strong.
Today, we tested our agility, strength,
and courage to overcome our fear of height.
These are the three skills I don’t own.
GOT IT!!
But if you test other skills, we will see.
So, he’s just yielding for now,
deceiving existing rangers.
I think the skill that makes me stand out
is the fact that I’m good at selecting teammates.
A NEW SKILL HERE
I can make a balance when choosing my team members.
They mustn’t be too bold or too vulnerable either.
Are you insulting me?
Nope.
What about your favorite mission?
Mond?
I enjoyed Rock Climbing.
It was pretty fun.
I like the first one.
Hit the balloon.
V ladder.
I like that Golden Card mission.
Same here.
So much fun.
I like archery.
I want to shoot more.
Well, I didn’t hit the target,
so I won’t count it as my favorite.
I like that mission that tested our balancing skill.
Mine is that Golden Card mission.
Rock Climbing.
That one (Golden Card).
Nice.
Same here.
It challenged our fear.
I like the first one.
Same?
V ladder?
I like them all.
I enjoy every moment spent with rangers.
GETS EMOTIONAL!!
It’s like you’re somehow leaving us?
No way.
Even if you kick me out, I won’t leave.
I like that balancing game.
Why?
Because we won?
Exactly.
I like that balancing game and archery.
Alright.
We have already got our skills adjusted.
All of us, 15 rangers, promise to do our best in any mission assigned.
BE PREPARED FOR FUN!
Please welcome our three new rangers.
OUR TEAM IS GETTING BIGGER!!
Thank you.
It’s a wrap for this week,
but throughout 2022, we have more fun and interesting missions awaiting.
For today, we express our thanks to our shooting location,
The Verona at Tub Lan!
We would like to invite you to enjoy your trip here.
The weather is amazing here, and they also offer you rooms to stay in.
The bed is so comfy.
It is perfectly a good choice for your family trip.
You can bring every family member along to take photos here because we have what?
We have a flower field here.
For anyone who is an adventurous traveler,
Also, those who enjoy taking photos couldn’t miss it either.
The Verona at Tub Lan in Prachinburi is only a two-hour drive from Bangkok.
Please make your visit.
Thank you.
Our time is up for today.
We’ll see you again every Saturday at 11 AM on GMM25.
It’s time for us, 15 rangers of 2022, to say goodbye.
Bye!
SORRY. HE’S NEW HERE.
Next week, meet our guests, Nanon, Khao Tung, Kay, PiPloy, and View
from 55:15 Never Too Late series.
They will walk on a coconut shell, play soccer and jump as high as possible.
How will their skills be?
Find out next Saturday at 11 AM on GMM25.