Ranger Gun, Sing, and Arms will challenge the height activity.
They need to stay balanced and hit the balloons with their knees.
The next mission, Harmony Balance Board, requires teamwork and balancing skills.
Let’s see if they will be able to pass the mission.
The following mission requires arm and leg strength for rock climbing.
Then they have to use their brain to figure out the answers.
Let’s see how much they can improve their ranger skills.
Let’s check it out in School Rangers: Intro to Rangers.
Before watching this week's episode, let’s take a time machine to last week's episode for a recap of their performance.
They kicked off with a workshop to get to know the new rangers and learn about each other.
You lost!
The first one to be eliminated is White.
Do you remember that one ranger had so much fun in the game that he ripped his pants?
Because of his overacting, Nicky got into trouble.
His pants were ripped into a big hole.
And these are Dior!
They’re not used to strenuous work, huh?
He sacrificed himself for laughter and fun.
Please give Nicky a round of applause.
After the workshop,
it was time for them to get change and boost their energy in the real mission ‘The Higher, The Louder’.
In the first round, the new rangers were selected to show their skills that would surprise the veteran rangers.
Would it be a good surprise or a bad one? We needed to wait and see.
First, be careful.
P’ First, be careful.
Mix, keep going.
Take it easy.
Earth was moving forwards at a fast speed.
He was hitting the targets nonstop.
He was too strong.
Take it easy.
After taking the time machine, there is no time for a break.
To become a good ranger, they need to strike while the iron is hot.
If you are ready, let’s go.
Are you confident?
I’m nervous.
The victory is in front of you.
Sure.
Your name is Sing. You should speed up.
HE RECEIVES AN ENCOURAGEMENT.
That’s good encouragement.
Are you scared?
Stop talking. Let’s begin.
After the whistle sound, Sing doesn’t waste his time.
Keep moving.
Keep going.
HE IS REALLY INTO THE GAME.
Moving fast.
Sing is moving towards the other end.
He hits the balloons left and right.
Being agile like a rat.
Being agile like a mus.
HERE COMES A MUS.
He seems to lose his balance a bit. He needs to stay focused.
That’s fast.
When he can focus again, his steps continue at ease.
Take it easy.
Sing loses his balance again at this step.		How will the game end?
THIS IS EXCITING.
Be careful.
Keep going.
Sing is getting close to the finish line.
It’s only a few steps away from the last balloon.
Faster. Faster than a cheetah.
HE LOOKS DISAPPOINTED.
It’s neck-to-neck.
You’re so good. I didn’t know you would be this good.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I’m pretty good.
You didn’t scream at all. How did you feel?
It wasn’t that scary but the boards were shaking.
I think I was doing alright.
IT WASN’T BAD.
We need to see how fast the other two teams will be.
I don’t think I was neither fast nor slow.
I’m not afraid if the height is this high.
I just don’t like wavering and thrilling feelings of it.
THIS IS A PIECE OF CAKE.
Now, it’s up to the other teams whether they will be faster than me.
You were going fast.
Chimon, do you think who was faster? P’ Sing or P’ Mix?
Please define Mix’s speed.
It’s a kind of fast.
It’s quite fast.
Sing was pretty fast.
The other teams were faster.
HOW SO?
To be honest, they both did well.
Are you giving me a kiss after a kick?
Good job.
He hasn’t done anything.
CALM DOWN.
You need to be fast.
Fight on, P’ Gun.
Fight on, Gun.
Faster, Faster.
Do you see it?
From the beginning, Gun is blasting the balloons nonstop.
Nothing can stop him.
He keeps moving forwards.
It’s okay. Don’t pay attention to the hands.
Go, go, go!
SPEEDY MOUSE.
What is happening to Gun? It seems like he is having a problem.
He needs to speed up.
Keep going.
He is getting close to the finish line.
Don’t give up, Mini Mouse.
Heading towards the last balloon. Go, Go, Go!
That’s so fast.
That’s super fast.
EVERYONE IS SHOCKED.
Is this someone who said he was scared?
You’ve never disappointed me.
I was scared that I might lose.
You were scared that you might lose.
I was nervous because Earth was very fast.
So I felt that I need to be fast too. I’m not sure if I was as fast as Earth.
There was a small problem in the middle. I couldn’t break a balloon.
Let’s wait and see how well I did.
Great job.
Was I fast?
Yes. Your speed is similar to Earth’s.
Well done. You’ve never disappointed me.
THE BIG BROTHERS KEEP PRAISING HIM.
We picked the right players.
First did better than I had expected.
Gun was as good as I had expected.
This is what it is called ‘follow belt’.
What is it?
As expected.
‘Follow belt’ (literally translation), don’t forget to share it.
Arm is mad that I said that he was a perfect man.
So he is very serious about the game.
He said he will reclaim his title this year. Let’s see if he can do it.
You will win.
Wait. That’s their team.
I ENJOY IT TOO MUCH.
Arm looks stressed.
I’m tired already.
P’ Arm, the worst thing is that you are defeated by First.
This is your honor, P’ Arm.
YOU CAN’T LOSE.
P’ Arm, don’t let them win. Show them your move.
HE SHOWS HIS FIGHTING SPIRIT THROUGH A SMILE.
Faster, faster.
Our perfect man starts off with a bit of difficulty.
He is a bit shaking. Please send him support.
This is your honor.
Be careful.
He continues smoothly.
This step is a big challenge. Every player made mistakes here.
Faster.
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT.
He’s heading towards the last balloon.
That’s neck-to-neck.
It’s quite tiring and tense.
I think I did well.
Along with Earth’s good performance earlier, our team did double well.
They did great. Both of them used only 25 seconds.
Gun is the only one who was faster than them.
But 25 seconds are considered very fast.
Gun is petit but very talented.
There’s one thing I’m worried about.
What is it?
I’m worried about Team B.
Will they be able to revive their fighting spirit?
I feel bad for them.
True.
They made a mistake from the beginning.
We already know how it’s going to end.
Please reveal the result, Godji.
In the first round between Earth, First, and Mix.
Let’s cross our fingers.
There’s nothing to hope for.
One of them used 55 seconds.
WHO IS HE?
That person is…
…Mix
You did well.
First used 47 seconds.
That was close.
Earth used 25 seconds.
WELL DONE.
In the 1st round,
Team C receives 3 points.
Team A receives 2 points.
Team B receive 1 point.
We got 2 points.
In the 2nd round, Sing used 34 seconds.
That was fast.
IT’S NOT BAD.
Arm used 25 seconds.
The time they both used is equal to the time that Mix used.
Gun Atthaphan used…
…22 seconds.
Team A receives 3 points.
Team C receives 2 points.
Team B receives 1 point.
The total points of Team A and Team C are 5 points.
Team B has 2 points.
Gun is great.
1, 2, 3. Hey, Hey, Hey!
Show your team spirit.
Hey, hey, hey.
What do you think about their performance in the 1st mission of Intro to Rangers episodes?
Both the veteran and rookie rangers showed off the skills that they have.
This is just the beginning. Many missions are waiting for them.
To be perfect rangers, they need to have not only agility but also teamwork.
So we prepare this mission for them.
This mission requires balancing skills.
But balancing skill is only one of the skills required for the game.
The other main skill required is teamwork.
I have done some research by watching the 200 episodes of our show.
The team which had good teamwork always won.
THE FACT IS CONFIRMED.
So I want to ask every team, do you think your team has good teamwork?
Let’s begin with Team A.
The teamwork of Team A is incomparable.
Among GMMTV artists, Nicky and Leo represent a long-lasting friendship.
They have been through good and bad together for a long time.
So our team has great teamwork.
What about Team B?
Since we have no other skill, we should have teamwork.
We also have an ace couple.
Who?
P’ White and P’ Sing.
THEY ARE NOT BACKING DOWN.
But you cannot leave me out from the team.
Right, then the team wouldn’t be complete.
It has to be White, Mond, and Sing.
I have to say that he adds weight to the team.
He helps keep the balance.
I’ll wait and see how you are doing in the game.
Alright.
I’m going crazy.
What about Team C?
I think my team has a great balance.
Did you see that New did the handstand when we had lunch?
He likes to do pushups as well.
Mond is also someone special. If he
didn’t have balance skills, he wouldn’t be able to build up his body like this.
Arm, we don’t need to worry about him because he’s a perfect man.
I ride a surf skate.
Why don’t you talk about yourself?
I want to talk about others first.
HE TRIES TO GET AWAY FROM THIS.
I have Meniere’s disease.
Really?
I’m not sure but I’m very bad at anything that requires balancing skills.
Okay, I get it.
I’M ROOTING FOR YOU.
Thank you for choosing me to be a part of your team.
I’m very glad that I’m in Team C today.
Let’s see how teamwork is related to this game.
Let’s check out the rules of the game.
The rules of the balancing board.
Each team will send three players to play.
They need to stand and balance the board not to touch the ground for 5 seconds.
The team which can successfully do it in 90 seconds will receive 3 points.
If they can do it in 2 minutes, they will receive 2 points.
If they can do it in 3 minutes, they will receive 1 point.
If they fail, they will receive no point.
In this game, teamwork is very essential.
Now, you know the rules.
This game does not require only teamwork.
The weight of the players also plays an important role in the game.
It can affect the result.
It will affect the balaence.
Balance.
Who will you send to play the game?
Let’s start with Team A.
The weight of each member in my team is not much different because we already talked about it.
So it doesn’t matter who we will send to play the game.
Am I right, Nicky?
Yes.
But among all the rangers, I think New will have the best performance in this game.
Why?
Because he is well-known internationally.
He is New Balance.
I don’t think this game is hard for us.
Here.
Here and here.
THEY ALL ARE THE ACES.
We need a young guy to balance between two old men.
Do you think how much time do you need to make it?
Three
Seconds?
Days.
THAT’S TOO LONG.
Team B.
Chimon and I have similar weights.
We will use a pin in the middle to balance us.
I’m the most secure pin in the team.
But you fell when you went to the restroom earlier.
No, I will be the pin.
Let’s move on to that team.
I’ll be the man in the middle in both rounds.
I’ll let the other two take care of the rest.
Who are they?
Our members’ weights are 70, 70, 66 and 67 kg.
We will keep the baelance. So wait and see how it’s going to be.
No one corrects my word.
Balance!
I don’t know what Team A is thinking.
Team B seems to think too much.
Team C is very confident.
Let’s see how we are doing in the game.
Rock, paper, scissors?
The loser will play first, right?
Rock, paper, scissors.
We will play last.
If we lose and have to play first, we will be at disadvantage.
You are talking too much.
Let’s do rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors
What will you show?
I don’t know.
No, don’t do this.
Turn around.
There are many people. Stop flirting.
Rock, paper, scissors
He shows rock.
The order of the team playing the game is Team B, Team C, and Team A respectively.
Let’s go.
Let’s hear the first team who will be the first to play this game talks about their feelings.
Are you confident?
They are so confident that their hands sweat a lot.
Okay, are you ready?
Get on.
I can’t.
Okay.
Then slowly move towards the center.
The players of Team B are already on the board.
They are trying to find the balance.
P’ Sing moves towards the center.
No, we can’t do this.
We need to transfer the weight.
HE IS SO STIFF.
I won’t say anything otherwise the board will shake.
Let’s start again. We need to transfer the weight.
THEY ARE GOING IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
1, 2, 3.
They are struggling at the beginning but this time they can keep the balance for 3 seconds.
This is a good start.
Let’s start again. We need to transfer the weight.
1, 2, 3.
Don’t start yet.
Do it slowly.
Push it your way.
If the board is about to lose its balance, you need to push your side.
1, 2, 3.
Push your side.
You need to fight my weight.
If it’s coming my way, you need to push.
Okay.
1, 2, 3, go!
Not yet. I can’t.
After they can keep the balance for 3 seconds, they seem to be unable to keep the balance for more than 1-2 seconds.
Keep trying.
Who will control the balance?
Only one person should be responsible for transferring the weight.
THEY ARE DISCUSSING THE STRATEGY.
Right. The man in the middle has to do it.
How can I help?
It’s hard.
1, 2, 3.
THEY ALMOST MAKE IT.
They can keep the balance for 3 seconds once again.
They almost made it.
Keep working together and find the balance, Team B.
Push towards the back.
How should we help them?
There’s nothing we can do.
THEY ARE REALLY STRUGGLING.
1, 2, 3.
Sing, push.
I think you need to move towards the center.
THEY ARE ROOTING FOR THE TEAMMATES.
1, 2.
THIS TAKES TOO LONG.
Tell me when you’re done.
I think it will take a while for this team to make it.
The other rangers are watching them closely.
I want to hear that they finally make it to 5 seconds.
You are close.
Don’t get angry.
This is hard.
THEY LOOK STRESSED.
Fight on.
Team B already spent 90 seconds in the game.
Now, they can change the players but the points they can receive will go down to 2 points.
1, 2, 3.
They can keep the board above the ground for 3 seconds now.
Let’s cheer on Team B.
4, 5.
They finally made it.
But before they can make it, they spent some time in trial and error.
They kept shaking to the right and left.
The closest they could get to the goal was that they could keep the balance for 3 seconds.
In the end, with their never-ending effort, they finally made it.
Team C, you saw an example, which can be either good or bad, from Team B.
What’s our strategy?
Off looks so nervous.
We will let P’ Off control everything.
Sure.
Clockwise moment equals anticlockwise moment.
HE IS AN EXPERT ON THE THEORY.
New,
come to this side and help lift Arm up.
I’ll lift him onto the board.
Are you going to start now? Are you ready?
I’m very ready.
Off, standing in the middle.
On the beam?
Yes.
If you are ready, Team C steps upon the board.
Show them how good you are.
We almost got it.
P’ Arm, keep your legs wide.
VERY FOCUSED.
P’ Arm, move a little further.
Hold on to me.
P’ Arm, push.
Why P’ Arm is heavy?
1, 2.
P’ Arm, push.
1, 2, 3.
They almost made it several times.	But they can only keep the balance for only 1-2 seconds.
When will they make it to 5 seconds?
1, 2.
You need to move a bit to that side.
Okay, wait a sec.
Go.
It looks like they are sbhooting a magazine.
You are having fun teasing them.
Those on the board need to stay focused. Be careful not to lose your focus because of the teasing.
Let’s find the balance first.
Push.
Handsome guys want to do good deeds on the weekend.
Off stays in the middle.
Mond, transfer your weight to the center.
This team has started counting 1 several
times but they should move to 2 and 3.
I think the man in the middle needs to spread his legs to keep the balance.
Why can’t you do it?
Wait a sec.
Should the man in the middle spread his legs?
Let’s try it.
THEY ARE CHANGING THEIR PLAN.
They are changing their position.
Let’s give it a try. Things may get better.
90 seconds has passed. You can change the players if you want.
New, do you want to give it a try?
90 seconds have passed.
Team C changes their plan by sending New in to fix the situation.
Let’s see how they are doing.
Only two of us can’t do it.
1, 2.
Almost got it.
You need to stay still and I’ll control the balance.
1, 2, 3, 4.
They finally reach 4 seconds.
They are in the right direction.
Stay still. I’ll control it.
Go.
Wait a sec.
After New stepped in, they look promising.
1, 2, 3.
Only 2 seconds are left. They need to keep the balance.
Will they be able to do it?
4, 5.
They have lost many sweats before they accomplish the mission.
In the beginning, they were very confident.
As time passed, they became uncertain.
They also changed the player in the middle of the game.
That’s why they are called ‘braggers’.
My team has a good balance.
It was not easy for the first two teams.
So let’s give them a break to calm down and improve their mood.
Then let’s see Team A’s performance in the next break. We will see if they doing well or not.
Team A may be on the rise, but this game could be a little intimidating.
It is obvious that the previous two teams were having a hard time with it.
It looks like Team A is ready to play.
How you doing, Team A?
My team is obviously stronger.
And we spent so long to complete this game.
NOT A COMPLIMENT?
I thought you were complimenting us.
Let’s see how Team A will do.
Since there are many elderly people, I wonder how it’ll be for them.
LOOKING DOWN ON TEAM A.
Looking down on us like that could be a mistake.
How’s it a mistake?
We’re right.
It is a mistake. I’ll show you not all old people are inefficient.
UNDER PRESSURE.
And?
They are capable!
You get on it.
Now, my turn.
And then you get on it.
Slowly balancing the weight.
ROOTING FOR THEM.
Stand just like P’Leo.
This team looks like they’ve got a good plan with Nanon taking the lead.
Try balancing it.
P’Leo, your balance.
Alright, slowly.
Keep calm, everyone. In three, two, one.
The plank’s balancing nicely right there, but let’s see how it’ll turn out.
One, two, three, four, five.
And they did it!
CONFUSION.
That was fast.
OVER THE MOON.
After seeing the failures of the previous teams, Team A, led by Nanon, came up with a plan right away.
They’ve got teamwork, good leadership, and great cooperation.
And it paid off just as the genius team expected.
Told you this game isn’t about strength.
It’s all about balance.
These two have been on earth longer so they know where the balance is.
WHAT ARE THEY LOOKING AT?
That’s why my team did better.
I didn’t wanna say anything much.
So proud.
THEY DID IT.
That was just practice for them to get the gist of the game.
Each team still has one more chance at it.
Pick your best members, boys!
We lost them last time. But this time, we’ll win.
I know how to play this game now!
If you’re ready, jump on board.
No need to rush. Just take it slow.
White, move your feet a little.
Go left, go left.
Up, up.
It doesn’t look like Team B will be on equilibrium any time soon.
All they do is keep touching the ground.
A little to the left.
They look like sumo wrestlers.
Oi, watch your face.
ROOTING HARD.
Their longest record so far is one second. They could be in trouble.
Let’s just dance.
ENCOURAGING CHEERS.
Do your best!
One, two, three, four.
Their new record is four seconds. Looks like they’ve got the gist of it.
Heave ho, heave ho, boys!
Just a little. Slowly.
You’ve got the rhythm down, we don’t need to change players.
In one, two, three. To the left. Right. Left.
Stay on the left.
A LITTLE MORE.
One, two.
THEY’RE IN TROUBLE.
You’re getting there.
One, two.
Calm down.
One, Two.
Looks like they’re almost there.
Three, four, five.
Yay!
That wasn’t an easy feast for them at all.
They were curled up together on the plank, touching the floor left and right.
The other guys were kept on the tips of their toes rooting for Team B.
But now it’s time for Team C to play.
Go!
I’ll get on it first.
This team relies on their strength and their coordination.
Wait, you guys try to stay still.
It’s impossible. I’m 60kg in weight while he 66.
MISCALCULATION.
I’ll handle the balance, you guys stay still.
One, two.
I didn’t stand like them. I turned this way.
One.
Sorry, Off.
One, two.
They started off so cool and balancing,
but now they keep rocking left and right. That isn’t so promising.
One, two, three.
That was three seconds down. They’re gonna make it.
Four.
Uh-oh, and they’re falling over. That was only one second short. Start over.
Do it again.
One, two, three, four.
Four seconds again. Can they do it this time?
Five.
And they did!
Good job.
That was beautifully done, Team C!
Their plan was better than their first try.
It might take a while to find their
equilibrium but it was smooth sailing from there.
Even after the count of five, they could still hold the plank off the ground for a few more seconds.
Good job!
Keep your eyes on us, children.
Don’t jinx it.
Adults aren’t flustered about this kinda thing.
IS THAT SO?
Still water runs deep.
Let’s row a boat. Row, row, row.
Only joking.
I’ve given my knowledge to the new generation.
Get on it.
Okay. Slowly.
Team A is in position. With Nanon at the helm, there is no need for worry.
First, keep your feet together.
Gun, your feet, too.
Closer.
O		LOOKING FOR THE BALANCE.
One, two, three.
See that? Is history about to repeat itself?
Four, five.
Yay!
MORE CONFUSION.
Who did better? You or them?
The word “fluke” isn’t in our dictionary.
What’s their secret? The first try was quick enough, but they did even better this time.
This game really belongs to Team A.	They sure got everyone dumbfounded.
Maybe they should quit being rangers and have a career in a balancing competition.
It’s all about planning.
Other teams just go for it, but we discuss our strategy.
You can see we didn’t stand the same way they did.
They chose to face forward, but we balanced the weight on both sides,
and let the guy in the middle handle the rest.
We trust each other.
If you really paid attention, both times,
it was Nanon who controlled the balance.
We really gotta give it to him this time around.
RESPECT FOR NANON.
I knew we would win from the moment I picked my teammates.
You planned this?
IS THAT SO?
I knew it from the moment I picked you.
You’re hogging the credits, dude.
Our team looks like we’ve got nothing up our sleeves.
Can you guys be sure we’re not gonna lose today?
Of course.
I’m certain we won’t lose. But I can’t say we’ll win.
Do you love this team?
I love this team.
That’s not what he said when we were picking teammates.
From this game, Team B and Team C receive four points each.
4 POINTS.
The MVP of this game, Team A, receives six points!
ALL TO THEMSELVES.
That was two games down and they’ve showcased their skills.
Now let’s look at their total scores.
Team A is in the lead with 11 points.
SO COOL.
Team C is not far behind with nine points.
NOT BAD.
Lastly is Team B with six points.
DO BETTER.
That’s not so far behind.
What a great feeling it is that our team has a competition.
What do you mean “a competition”, Leo?
Not a single team could take us.
THEY’RE BRAGGING.
You know what, Team B and C could combine their points and still don’t come up to us.
And the teamwork game is over.
Some teams even tried to use maths to help them play.
And the results are just as you’ve seen it.
It is time to test their climbing skills in the next break.
Alright, the next game requires lower and upper body strengths and also knowledge.
Becoming a ranger really is full of obstacles, but otherwise they wouldn’t be the perfect rangers.
The next game is rock climbing!
EXCITED CHEERS.
And what you need to win this is bravery, confidence, and craziness.
Which Team has it all?
Our team.
Excuse you, P’Tay. Look at our builds.
Who’s got bravery?
Me. Everyone here.
We’re bold.
THEY DON’T LOOK THAT WAY.
It was dead quiet.
Yeah, we’re brave.
We are!
If you’re really brave then your team go first.
Mond, you go.
LIKE HE’S PLAYING HOT POTATO.
What if we’re afraid of height, can we climb it horizontally?
THAT’S TOO ADVANCED.
Honestly, I’m concerned for this team.
Why?
Well, they don’t look like they can make it.
No need to be concerned for us.
We’re definitely not gonna make it.
Oh, okay.
Hey.
DO NOT UNDERESTIMATE.
You’d never know, right?
I’ll do it.
Really?
I did it once.
I’ve got deja vu.
I missed that time.
Can I just jump off? I’ve had enough with this. I’m scared!
But this time, it could work.
I’m not saying I can do it, I just gotta try.
Show them what we’ve got.
Of course.
What about you over there in Team A?
I’ll do it.
Don’t do it, Gun. I don’t want you getting tired.
First, you do it.
We gotta learn from our mistakes and our fears.
I’m afraid of heights but I’ll do it.
LET’S TRY!
I’ll overcome my fear.
To victory.
Today, my team will come out on top.
Let’s say your fear was right in front of you. Overcome it.
Don’t wanna.
FAILURE.
Why do we need strength and power to win this game? Let’s see what the rules are.
The rules of the rock climbing game.
Each team sends in one player to climb the boulder to get to the clues.
Each time they reach a clue, the player reads the keyword out loud for their teammates.
After they get all the keywords, the player must come down to write the correct answer on the board.
The team with the best time record wins the game.
And that was the rules of the game.
Rock climbing needs lower body strength, do you guys have any?
Yeah!
Do you?
I’m about to fold over.
GET UP!
You have to put up a fearless look.
Let’s pretend we didn’t hear that.
P’Tay, you gotta be braver.
Act tough, P’Tay. Puff your chest.
THAT’S YOUR BRAVE FACE?
Adorable.
What about Team C, you got any strength in your legs?
Of course.
Excuse you, I do squats while carrying a 180kg weight on me.
I can do that, too, man. But I’ll black out.
HE SHOULD HAVE JUST STAYED QUIET!
Hey, listen to what my big brothers here can do.
What’s wrong, man?
He’s vexed.
CALM DOWN.
You said you carry, what, 180kg while squatting?
That’s nothing.
My brother here used to be a football player.
His lower body is mad strong.
He could break a ball with a kick.
TIME TO SHOW ’EM.
Oh, we’re so gonna win this.
He can get from here to up there in a leap.
WOW!
His kicks rival even those of Zlatan’s!
He could do 20 speed squats in a breath.
Don’t even mention step over, ’cause he sure can do.
KEEP GOING.
JUST SHUT YA TRAP ALREADY, BRO.
In other words, my team is very good.
VERY BELIEVABLE.
Now that we know the rules, who will be playing for your teams in the first round?
The first round is all about timing. The second round is English vocabulary.
For the first round, we’re sending our little hamster.
What about you guys in Team B?
Alright, I’ll go first.
I’ll take Gun down this round.
So we’re sending New.
Can we send Nicky, too?
To the hospital, that is.
HE PLAYED TOO MUCH.
I am heaving through my lungs.
Alright, let the game begin!
Hey, don’t get too worked up.
Say something.
Well…
Yeah.
How fast will you go?
Not so fast because this is actually a bit scary.
He said he was scared.
From a distance, it doesn’t look tall. But standing right underneath it now, it is tall.
P’Gun is our only hope.
’Cause there’s no one else you can count on.
THAT WAS MEAN!
You’re underestimating us. We can still count on Leo.
Let’s switch places right now.
Don’t waste your time, man. Come back.
STAY PUT.
Gun wouldn’t give up his place, too. He scooted away from you just now.
Go, go.
Go slowly.
No need to rush, Gun. Go easy. Don’t listen to Leo.
Gun took no time to reach the first clue at all.
Amphawa.
Amphawa. We know that.
It’s in Chiang Rai?
It’s not.
Gun keeps on climbing.
It’s not in Suphanburi.
It’s in Samut Sakhon.
I know it.
In Samut Songkhram.
Mackerel.
Mackerel? From Mae Klong.
WHERE IS IT?
I know this, too.
Khlong Khon, what’s that?
Just get down here.
With his mini size, climbing isn’t his problem at all.
He was so fast to get to the clues which say, “Amphawa,” “mackerel,” and “Khlong Khon.”
What will be the answer Gun and his team come up with?
It’s Samut Sakhon.
How do you spell that?
S-M…
The whole team is helping him spell out the correct word.
T. Write T.
S-A-K-H-O-N.
Let’s ring the bell.
Oh, they got it wrong. Think again.
It’s Samut Songkhram.
S-O-N-G-K-H-R-A-M.
Okay!
Told you it wasn’t correct.
Mackerel from Khlong Khon?
Mackerel from Khlong khon and Amphawa.
From Mae Klong, mostly.
Was it tiring climbing up there?
Yeah. It took a lot of energy. My legs are burning right now.
It kinda felt slippery when I was climbing.
Could you guess the answer while you were climbing?
Not at all. I didn’t even think about it, only read it aloud.
I was only aiming to get up there as fast as I could, hoping the team would take care of the rest.
Was it difficult? If you’re not afraid, then it’s not supposed to be.
Hey, White. I’ve got high hopes for you. I hope you’ll do great in this game.
You’ll get to the top.
For rock climbing?
Of course.
If I’d be climbing up anywhere, it’d be right behind you all.
Let’s climb together, then.
Just like that.
One step at a time.
He’s getting further from the ground.
Don’t fret the heights.
SOMETHING FLEW BY.
It broke off.
It seems White has lost his balance.
It’s alright.
Stay calm.
Football field.
Keep climbing, White.
Could it be Buriram?
Could be.
Is it, though?
Wait for the next clues.
Muangthong.
Oi, football fields are common in every freaking province.
White suddenly slipped off. What matters now is if he can remain focused and keep going.
It’s alright, White.
EVERYONE IS ROOTING.
You can keep going.
It’s alright, White.
EVERYONE IS ROOTING.
You can keep going.
You’re doing amazing.
It’s okay. Keep going.
White, stay strong. Stay strong!
Keep holding on, White. You’ll get there soon.
You can do it.
ENCOURAGEMENTS KEEP POURING.
DETERMINED.
You can!
Do it!
Prasart Phanom Rung.
It’s Buriram!
Keep going.
Get the next one and jump off.
Meatballs.
Get down here.
Just let go.
Although the climb was rocky and slippery for White,
but with his determination, he got all the clues that say, “football field,” “Prasart Phanom Rung,” and “meatballs.”
Let’s see what their answer is.
Quickly.
The climb was rough for him from start to finish.
But now he’s got a pen in his hand and it’s time to write his answer.
B-U-R-I-R-A-M.
Ring it.
Football field.
There’s a football club, Buriram United.
Buriram United.
Prasart Phanom Rung, the famous historical place.
And lastly, meatballs.
It’s Lisa’s favourite snack from her hometown.
GOOD JOB!
And so the answer is…
Buriram!
How was it, facing your defeated fear?
It was challenging, not easy at all.
My grips weren’t strong enough to hold on.
Of course I felt a little shaken since it wasn’t something I’m used to.
But compared to last time…
You did much better.
Last time, White gave up after he slipped.
But this time, he kept pushing forward.
When you slipped, were you scared?
Did you realise there was a safety line on you?
I knew it was safe, but it gave me a fright anyway.
I have never done rock climbing in my entire life. This is my first time.
REALLY?
Are you joking?
I have really never tried.
But I saw a photo of you rock climbing, P’New?
He was just lying. He’s good at it.
I’m scared, really.
Do you even have any strength, New?
Not really.
New’s good. I’ve seen him climb.
You can do it, P’New.
New proceeds nimbly upward.
How could he just do that?
Looks difficult.
Mon Bridge.
That’s in Kanchanaburi.
That was one clue down. He’s heading towards the next.
It’s in Tak.
Or Chanthaburi?
Erawan Falls.
Maybe Nakhon Nayok?
Khwae Noi River.
That was three clues down very easily.
He was very agile.
And the clues are “Mon Bridge,” “Erawan Falls,” and “Khwae Noi River.”
What province would that be, Team C?
K-A-N.
C-H-A-N-A.
And Buri.
Ring it.
Well done.
He was so quick.
What are the clues again?
First, Mon Bridge.
Then, Erawan Falls.
And lastly…
Khwae Noi River.
How was this week’s episode?
That was two missions down for our new rangers.
The first game was a feast of height and speed,
and Team A and C sent their strongest rangers to conquer it.
No wonder the two teams won that game and got a head start.
The second game was all about balance,
with Team A easily snatching the first place.
Even with different players on the plank, it was still smooth sailing for Team A.
We really gotta give it to them.
We can say that practice really makes perfect.
Special thanks to the location for this training camp for our rangers at The Verona at Thap Lan in Prachinburi.
It is only a few hours away from Bangkok and it’s got great weather and great hotels.
A perfect trip for families and anyone adventurous, since they’ve got all these fun obstacle games.
There is also a beautiful garden for photography enthusiasts, too. Thank you for the hospitality.
Next week, we’re still here with our special episodes: Intro to Rangers.
It takes more than willpower to become the perfect rangers.
Stay tuned and root for the last team’s rock climbing challenge and another mission which tests who’s a great shot.
Lastly, it is time to push them to their limits to see who’s actually got the guts.
We will see you in seven days. Good day!